Krish Naik: Hmm, alright.
Krish Naik: Alright, so in the last class, we have already gone through the part for the deployment, okay? So, let me define today's agenda.
Krish Naik: And then I will come to yesterday's topic, don't worry.
Krish Naik: All good.
Krish Naik: Okay, so today, we'll be discussing Lama Index, and the last class, we have gone through the first project.
Krish Naik: And a few things with, like, Langsmith, Docker, okay, then for CI and CD, with GitHub Actions, and AWS AppRunner.
Krish Naik: Today's discussion, a complete new framework that we'll be starting. Again, famous, I can say. Llama Index is also widely used. I think that in some cases, Llama is also very powerful as compared to LandChain.
Krish Naik: So, today's idea is getting familiar with the syntax of Llama much more. The syntactical, and to show you, the same things happen just like inline check. But here, I feel, the pipeline structure that Llama provides is much modular structure.
Krish Naik: And easy to, work with, as compared to LanChain. Langchain is, like, I feel that anybody starting, for them, LanChain is good. But once LandChain is done, then the next step. For advanced users, I feel Llama Index is always a better option.
Krish Naik: But again, you have to understand, it's just like Keras and PyTorch. The same thing which can be done in Keras, okay, it can be done in PyTorch. Okay, so, similar frameworks.
Krish Naik: Now, next week, a few important topics that we'll be talking about, like, advanced chunking strategies, hybrid search, re-ranking, ID. Okay, so those things we'll be talking next week.
Krish Naik: Much more conceptual topics, I can say. Very, very important, because now, my idea will be, you guys know about NAVRAC.
Krish Naik: And we will move towards advanced track.
Krish Naik: Okay, so that will be my idea, that you guys have understood the name one, and step by step, we will take few components. For example, chunking, then we will try to bring hybrid, re-rank, and ID. Similarly, like, fusion will come going forward in the other classes.
Krish Naik: No, no, no extra classes.
Krish Naik: No extra glasses.
Krish Naik: Okay, so it's simply, like, Saturday and next Saturday, Sunday, we'll be talking about this. But today, let's get familiar with Lama. Now, tell me, the last class deployment, like, how many have done it? Once the video was uploaded into the portal, how many of you have done it?
Krish Naik: Like, I know many of you have done it in the class, but I feel like more than 50% has not done. So, those 50%, you can let me know.
Krish Naik: Little bit, like, how many got stuck?
Krish Naik: Okay, no Santosh. No holiday.
Krish Naik: I have holidays only on 25th, 31st, and 1st. It's only 3 days.
Krish Naik: I got stuck at Dockerfile image, done 12th grade, done, done.
Krish Naik: Okay, again, Raul Barrier got stuck, I will try later today, okay. Alright, fine, see, like, today in the dark class, also, you can ask me the questions, no issue. But, please try, at least, by yourself.
Krish Naik: Because that CI part will be the same. Now, I can add something in CI. So, if you really look into the reference project, like, last Sunday, the report that I have shared, there you have test cases also.
Krish Naik: See, now, the idea is to extend yourself. It's not like only keep limit to the things that I have only taught, but how to do the other integrations.
Krish Naik: So, I think let's take our desktop, I think this is 3 only, for sure.
Krish Naik: Just wait, I will take one GitHub repo for now.
Krish Naik: Where is my GitHub junk fees?
Krish Naik: Hmm, alright.
Krish Naik: Today's repo is fine, I'll be sharing with you, but, the things that I want to test by yourself, at least the things that I have not discussed.
Krish Naik: Alright, now this was the repo in the last class that I've shared.
Krish Naik: Now, you guys have already done the first part. Now, try to integrate a few more features. For example, I know that most of you don't work with test cases, but if you want to add.
Krish Naik: Because I have only added two things, the code formatter and linting. So please go into this and try to integrate them in your CI. All your test cases should pass through CI. So already you have the code, so at least try to do the testing.
Krish Naik: Okay, integrate it.
Krish Naik: And then see. So, if you look into my CI file.
Krish Naik: In the last class I have taken the CI file, it was much simplified.
Krish Naik: Where the…
Krish Naik: core objective was only to build the image and to test whether it's working or not. But what about your entire codebase?
Krish Naik: So, lint check, code formatters, these things I have kept in this CI file.
Krish Naik: Okay, as you can see, unit tests I have kept. So please, at least try to take this to the next level, from your side, because already I provided it's just only 2 to 3 lines of scripts that you need to add.
Krish Naik: Okay, please do it.
Krish Naik: Because going forward, Probably I might not use test cases. But you have to understand that in production, there will be some type of testing team, okay, and they will be working on that.
Krish Naik: Okay, so please do have check on these functionalities.
Krish Naik: I think the deploy.yml file is, same only, it's not a lot of difference here.
Krish Naik: But, the CI part was important, so I thought, like, once whoever has done the last class, please try to integrate these features also from your report.
Krish Naik: Alright.
Krish Naik: Vijit, we have RAG project class, and the RAG project queue, and A, the second one we need to try. Try the last one. Try the project one, not the class one. Class in class that we have done. Okay, because core functionality is the same, but some added features that I have done.
Krish Naik: Okay, so whoever has done the first step, please take the second step from your site.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, today's repo, let me share.
Krish Naik: I think it was Llama Freppu Spot.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: So, first of all, I think, yes, this is the one.
Krish Naik: I'm sharing it in the chat.
Krish Naik: Okay, Notion I will update after the class, so for now directly sharing the GitHub link here.
Krish Naik: to Asma Sultana, when you are getting this error, that the AppRunner ECR access role cannot be found. It means that it is not available. In the last class, I have already shown you
Krish Naik: Manually go and create the service, automatically that ECR access role will be created.
Krish Naik: Please refer to the last lecture, at least.
Krish Naik: Okay, so everybody please take a clone of the repo.
Krish Naik: I don't think I have any information, here, but, take the one for now.
Krish Naik: Please click clone, and then let me know.
Krish Naik: In the meantime, I think for my llama discussion.
Krish Naik: Let's first of all get the documentation. I think somewhere I'll be having the documentation opened, yes.
Krish Naik: I don't know, there is some issue in my system.
Krish Naik: In multiple editors, I'm getting a kernel crash issue today.
Krish Naik: Okay, I will try to sort it out, but let me know, sir, in the last…
Krish Naik: I was absent last week and didn't find the Landsmith configuration.
Krish Naik: Landsmith configuration yesterday, also, I have told…
Krish Naik: Just sign up to Langsmith, create a project, you will be getting the environment variables, just keep them in the .env file. Only that was the part.
Krish Naik: Yes, I will take that as a note for next week, okay? Bedrock, sage…
Krish Naik: Unless maybe later on. See, like, Bedrock is the main service, like, for air to bring the LLM, I can use Bedrock. SageMaker is totally different.
Krish Naik: SageMaker, if I'm teaching you machine learning, deep learning, working with LLMs, in those cases, I feel it's much more important. For RAG, SageMaker is not, I can say, the perfect surface. Only if you are working with AWS environments, then it makes your life easier.
Krish Naik: Everybody has taken the clone, please let me know.
Krish Naik: Amit is asking, is Dockerfile inside .vnv environment? No, it has to be outside. He always keep your Dockerfile in the root directory.
Krish Naik: Yeah, SageMaker doesn't fall in our case. If I'm working with deep learning, where I need GPU-based instances.
Krish Naik: In those cases, I feel it's much better. Otherwise, not so much useful.
Krish Naik: What are the relevant services in Azure? The same things that we have done it, you can do it in Azure also. Azure also has a container registry that you can use, and similarly, they have that Azure web app service, very similar to AppRunner.
Krish Naik: In GCP, again, artifact registry with Cloud Run. The same things tried from your site, I think only 3 lines of code that will change.
Krish Naik: And always remember that AWS CLI. Similarly, in Google Cloud, you have to do the installation of Google Cloud CLI. Similarly, in Azure also, because local authentication needs to be done. So, that part, please do explore.
Krish Naik: Alright, everybody, please let me know.
Krish Naik: The clone is taken, can we start with our discussion?
Krish Naik: Perfect.
Krish Naik: So, first of all, so from the official documentation page, we will start.
Krish Naik: So, little bit from the Llama, I can say, community. We have explored the Llama parse, which is only used for parsing.
Krish Naik: But now, we'll be focusing on the framework of Gen AI, okay, which is the Lama Index Framework.
Krish Naik: Now, when I'm talking for Llama Index, you have to think it's exactly same as lanjing.
Krish Naik: Built by different communities, but the core purpose. It means that the same thing that you can achieve in LanChain
Krish Naik: can be achieved in Llama Index.
Krish Naik: I hope everybody knows about Keras and PyTorch, the same thing, so here also it lies. Now the question comes, your data loaders, your vector stores.
Krish Naik: your embeddings, working with LLMs, all those things will come, step by step, like, I will be showing you a
Krish Naik: Now, the question comes for you, which one you want to use going forward.
Krish Naik: I feel that most of the times, LanChain does the job, 70%, but sometimes I feel Lama Indexes
Krish Naik: powerful as compared to Tangent. Now, those use cases, we'll be talking In today's class.
Krish Naik: Now, let me just increase the font here.
Krish Naik: So, this is also completely free framework. You can work with it. Now, the services in Llama Cloud are paid. So, whenever you look into the services of Llama Cloud, so there are multiple services
Krish Naik: And a lot of those services are in beta state, okay? But only these are paid, the top versions that I'm telling you, okay? Then… but everything which comes under the Lama Index framework, everything is open source, you can work with it.
Krish Naik: No issue, you don't need to pay any money.
Krish Naik: So, one of the leading frameworks for building LLM-powered agents over your data
Krish Naik: Okay, now, it has two separate engines, like, the RAG engine, as well as the chat engine. I'll be talking about those engines, but the same functionality is just like Landshake. You can simply build RAG,
Krish Naik: No, here they are talking about what is contest.
Krish Naik: Augmentation. Anybody knows about contest augmentation?
Krish Naik: Before context augmentation, you have to understand the part of context fusion, exactly where context fusion happens.
Krish Naik: Yes, how many of you know about context fusion? I think, probably somewhere I might have discussed.
Krish Naik: Otherwise, I will just take out my notes and tell.
Krish Naik: Okay, no idea. Alright, just wait, let me just connect my iPad, then I will start.
Krish Naik: So much.
Krish Naik: Oh, this is a rack batch.
Krish Naik: Template… Don't return.
Krish Naik: Just wait one minute.
Krish Naik: All right, so now let me connect to my iPad. I will just share the iPad screen by cable.
Krish Naik: I hope it is visible for everyone.
Krish Naik: In your RAT pipeline, if you remember, the first part was the output.
Krish Naik: operate driven.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: So, when the output of the retrieval, basically your chunks, probably, like, top K chunks or top 3 chunks, when you send that information into LLM, and then you get a complete, I can say, based on your prompt instructions, so here I will keep the prompt instructions.
Krish Naik: And then, finally, you get your output.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: Now, this place exactly where context fusion take place.
Krish Naik: Where you mix the context of your retriever with the context of LLM.
Krish Naik: plus the LNN.
Krish Naik: Okay, always remember that. So, a very similar thing, because once the idea of context fusion is clear, then comes the idea of context augmentation.
Krish Naik: And context fusion is common in every rack problem, because you will be using some type of LLM. It can be, like, localhosted, anywhere, or domain-specific LLMs, but the process of fusion has to be there.
Krish Naik: Okay, so the actual step, like, when this particular impression… so, before your final output, the context fusion takes place, and based on that, you will be getting your output.
Krish Naik: So, remember, context vision is one of the most common, techniques, I can say, where both of your context comes into the picture, and based on that, you're rephrasing, or the entire, I can say, the output that you will be getting, based on any type of instructions that will be passing through the prompt template.
Krish Naik: Now, let's come to context augmentation, a very similar
Krish Naik: Meaning, I can say. So, let's get back, I think this is desktop 3.
Krish Naik: So, first of all, they have also brought the idea of agents, similarly in Langchen 1v1.
Krish Naik: It's not same as augmentation, little bit different. In augmentation, other things also comes, like agents can also be brought into the picture.
Krish Naik: So, the first thing, if you look into the agents, there is a… Llama agents are also there.
Krish Naik: Okay. Just an agentic framework help.
Krish Naik: I think everybody knows about Langraph, which comes from the community of LangChain. Similarly, from the community of Llama, the Llama agent comes.
Krish Naik: similar features, just like Langraph, which you have.
Krish Naik: Now, the first thing, yes, workflows are there, so generally, like, using agentic workflows, you have to use Llama Agents, but right now, we are not talking from agent's perspective. We are much more focused towards RAG.
Krish Naik: Now, what is context augmentation? So, LLMs offers a natural language interface between the humans and the data. LLMs come pre-trained on huge amounts of publicly available data, but they are not trained
Krish Naik: on your data. Okay, so your data may be private or specific to the problem that you are trying to solve.
Krish Naik: which is behind APIs, or in SQL databases, or in some other document formats.
Krish Naik: Contest augmentation makes your data available to the LLM to solve the problem at hand.
Krish Naik: So, now see, when augmentation… oh, in simple meaning, what is the meaning of augmentation?
Krish Naik: As for in deep learning, if you have learned, what is augmentation?
Krish Naik: Data augmentation.
Krish Naik: from NLP perspective, or in computer vision prospect.
Krish Naik: everywhere we are doing, it's not, addition, it's not addition, rather than akhilith, right? Like, modification. On top of your original data, you will be doing some type of modification, or some type of transformations that we call.
Krish Naik: Okay, now the transformation depends upon what type of data. It can be image-based transformations or text-based transformations.
Krish Naik: And, the transformation will introduce some type of, I can say, nonlinearity.
Krish Naik: There will be some changes.
Krish Naik: Now, context augmentation makes your data available to solve the problem at hand. Llama Index provides the tools to build any or context
Krish Naik: augmentation use case from prototype to production. Our tools allow you to ingest, parse.
Krish Naik: Okay, index, process your data, and quickly implement complex query workflows, combining data access with LLM prompting. So here you can see all the features which are available in LanChain, the same thing that they are referring here.
Krish Naik: Okay. Now, a few things you have to understand. So, when I'm talking about the data ingestion phase, so generally what happens in a data ingestion field?
Krish Naik: I can see that, okay, I read the data, the first thing that happens, the parsing. Once the parsing is done, in the next step, chunks that comes. Once the chunks are available, then you will perform the index operation.
Krish Naik: So, here, they do have built pipelines. It means that within a pipeline, you can directly call all of your functions in one shot, and then you can build it. Okay, so really, the workflows are really good as compared to Langshan, I can say.
Krish Naik: The most popular example of context augmentation is REG. Okay.
Krish Naik: Because the actual thing that happens is basically the context fusion between your LLM and your actual data.
Krish Naik: So, it is one of the major frameworks which is widely used for any type of LLM-based application. You have, everything, like, data connectors are available, so SQL-based connectors here are also available. The same thing in line chain, because in our Project 2, we'll be talking about text-to-SQL tasks.
Krish Naik: Okay, so there I'll be, utilizing.
Krish Naik: this. Then comes your data indexes, then comes your query engines. Okay, so two types of engines that they have defined here. The first one is query, generally for rack that we use, and then if you want to build a complete chat interface, then you have chat engines.
Krish Naik: Agents are also available. In Langshan, we have not talked about agents. I think probably after, Module 9 or 10, when your, Langraph starts. Before Langraph, I'll be talking that in Langshan V1, they have brought
Krish Naik: agents, and it's very easy to work with those agents. How to do a deep research agent.
Krish Naik: Then comes your deep agents, deep thinking agents. Okay, so those things will come, but in the future model, because right now, I don't want to start with agents. Then, it has an observability and evaluation tool, okay, similar, like, in the Langchen ecosystem for observability, which tool has been used?
Krish Naik: You guys have already used it in the last project. What was the tool?
Krish Naik: Okay, it was Langsmith. So, here also another tool that will be coming. Then, similarly, they have evaluation, integrations. You can use RAGAS also, but yes, inbuilt integrations are also available for the evaluation of any, like, LLM applications, and majorly for RAG, I can say.
Krish Naik: Now, multiple use cases are there, as you can see, Q&A, chatbots, okay, document understanding and data extraction. So, really, the use cases are really good, you can look into. So, first of all, let's start with the installation part. Everybody, please create a new virtual environment.
Krish Naik: And do the installation of all the requirements that I…
Krish Naik: I think, in your requirements, how many requirements are there?
Krish Naik: Okay, I have removed all the versions, so please take the first step and create a virtual environment, and everybody play through the installation.
Krish Naik: Looking… alright.
Krish Naik: Jupiter is there fine.
Krish Naik: Everybody?
Krish Naik: Please complete it.
Krish Naik: Rishi done, what about others?
Krish Naik: Subhash is telling Ragas, yes, you can use RAGAS also for the same evaluation, doesn't matter. The integration of RAGAS is with any major frameworks.
Krish Naik: Hold.
Krish Naik: Now, in the ENV file, okay, so here I'm using OpenAI API key.
Krish Naik: Okay, so I've shared you the env.example, only a single OpenAI API key that you need to pass.
Krish Naik: Okay, so just to be sure you have configured your .env.
Krish Naik: Already shared.
Krish Naik: the GitHub link.
Krish Naik: I think everybody has taken the clone of the repo?
Krish Naik: all people, like, joining late, who are asking for the GitHub link now.
Krish Naik: Please join on time.
Krish Naik: Let me share the link.
Krish Naik: Again, in the chat.
Krish Naik: I have shared it.
Krish Naik: Everybody, please create the virtual environment and do the installation. I don't think there will be problem in the installation. I've done the installation more than 3 to 4 times. In Mac, I didn't face any issue.
Krish Naik: Anybody facing any issue?
Krish Naik: Although it was running good yesterday night. Alright, fine.
Krish Naik: I don't feel that you will be getting any errors. And by default, remember, we are picking everything from the recent ones. It means that all the latest releases for these…
Krish Naik: libraries that we will be using. So, I have not kept any version in requirement.txte. What will be… whatever will be the latest version, it will be picked up.
Krish Naik: And always remember also, like, I'm not showing you, but it's your job to check what is the version.
Krish Naik: Always remember this. You can do a pep list through that, or at least look into the project. When you look into the release history, you will see that frequent updates are here.
Krish Naik: Okay, like, 0.14.10, 0.14. Now, pick anything, like, right now, I think I'll be taking the latest one, but you can use, like, anything from 14.7, 14.8, they also work really good. No issues that I've faced.
Krish Naik: Joe already shared the GitHub link, again, you were asking.
Krish Naik: I'm sharing last time, please don't ask for GitHub links.
Krish Naik: Alright, Notion I will update later on, okay?
Krish Naik: Alright, now, asking for Python donations…
Krish Naik: Now, always remember this particular version, so just be around 14, more than, like, 14.5. I feel that you should be above the version. Few functionalities are newly added, so please be…
Krish Naik: On top of 14.5.
Krish Naik: Okay, so let's start with our notebook.
Krish Naik: So I hope for everybody the installation is done. Please let me know.
Krish Naik: Okay, 2 minutes.
Krish Naik: I think in 2 minutes, even, I can edit the machines.
Krish Naik: 2 minutes, alright, alright, I will wait.
Krish Naik: Why it takes so much time, generally? Like, to create a virtual environment.
Krish Naik: I can say that less than one minute it takes. If you're working with UV, if you're working with PIP, I know it will take a lot of time.
Krish Naik: Do we guys?
Krish Naik: It should be fast.
Krish Naik: Installing requirement… see, like, if I take an example in my case.
Krish Naik: Let me just, open wrap.
Krish Naik: Alright, like, comma…
Krish Naik: Okay, the installation is done. It should not take a lot of time. I hope you… everybody's using
Krish Naik: UV, because with UV, I don't think there will be any issues, that's why.
Krish Naik: Environment creation doesn't take time. Whoever is telling, like, at least in 2025, it becomes much faster.
Krish Naik: At least with UV, I know it's very, very fast. If you're not working with UV, Conda, PIP, they are pretty slow.
Krish Naik: And it depends upon the internet connection also. If you have a weak internet connection, the problem can be there.
Krish Naik: For everybody else's done, please let me know.
Krish Naik: Yes.
Krish Naik: All right, let me just quickly do it here.
Krish Naik: Alright, so let's start with the code execution.
Krish Naik: So, first of all, like, Llama Index, the same things that have been retained, so directly I want to jump into the code, but before that, like, the package structure, how they have done it.
Krish Naik: Okay, so just, I will increase the font. So, one is the Llama Index Core, which provides you the base abstraction. Similarly, you have a Langchen Core package.
Krish Naik: GIF?
Krish Naik: I think you guys remember about the Lanshan Core package.
Krish Naik: Okay, very similar. It means that all your base implementations, okay, those things are available, but no third-party integrations. For your third-party integrations, you have integration-specific packages, just like LanChain. It means that, okay, for quadrant, a separate package.
Krish Naik: For Chroma, a separate package. Similarly, if you want to bring some another LLM, for Anthropic, another package. For OpenAI, another package. For Hugging Face, another package, okay? So, those things, that comes.
Krish Naik: Then you have, Llama Index, the meta, where you have your bundle scores and default integration. So, generally, this meta actually comes under core only.
Krish Naik: Then, the structure here will be very, very modular. Okay, it's much more towards functional implementations here.
Krish Naik: Okay, I feel that,
Krish Naik: Landshain is also functional, but Llama Index is highly functional, as compared to Landshain, because in Lanshan, some things are loosely coupled, but here, at least I feel majorly, everything is kept as a module, which can be easily integrated into a pipeline.
Krish Naik: So, first of all, let's check with your imports, everyone. I hope it works for me. Yes, it's working.
Krish Naik: everybody check the first import, okay? And let's look into the imports now. First of all, we are using a vector store index, fine. I hope everybody understands what is the meaning of a vector store index.
Krish Naik: Yes, please let me know. What is the meaning of a vector store in text?
Krish Naik: In Langshan, you guys have already learned about that.
Krish Naik: You will perform an in-depth operation.
Krish Naik: Okay, for a vector store.
Krish Naik: Okay, now the vector store, yeah, you have to understand the vector DB can be different.
Krish Naik: Okay? But the core indexing operation, okay, for your chunks, that will be done through this service.
Krish Naik: Simple Directory Reader, how many of you remember this? A very similar implementation there in LandChain also?
Krish Naik: Directory Reader was the name, where I don't think you have the name of Simple Directory Reader, but it was only Directory Reader, okay? Then you have settings. Through settings, like, you'll be passing your LLM settings, embedding settings, those things.
Krish Naik: And finally, you have a document class. In Langshan, also, you have a document. So, for example, here also, I'll be creating some custom documents. In those cases, it will be useful.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: Then comes parsing. So, for parsers, so here, as you can see, Llama and text core mode parser. So, you have to remember, all of your splitting, like, in Langshan, there is a separate package, the LanChain text splitters. But here, everything is inbuilt in the core only.
Krish Naik: Okay, so lamaintext.core, node parser. From here, I am using one type of parsing mechanism, like the sentence splitter.
Krish Naik: Central splitter, it means that, based on sentences, the splitting operation that will take place.
Krish Naik: Now, as I'm working with OpenAI, so simply I've done the integration with OpenAI now.
Krish Naik: So, llamaindex.llms.openai, and for this, I have done the installation of the package.
Krish Naik: Okay, so this one. Llama Index LLMs OpenAI. Similarly, if you want to work with Anthropic, okay, I have kept it.
Krish Naik: Okay, now let's get back here.
Krish Naik: Now, for your embedding selection, from the same package, you will be using the OpenAI embedding.
Krish Naik: Now, in the next step, loading your environment variables, OS warnings, common boilerplate.
Krish Naik: So, I think for everybody, this part should be clear. So, in the next step, I'll be loading the environment variable.
Krish Naik: Now, let's start defining our global settings. Global settings refer to the things that are fixed. You don't want to change them. For example, LLM selection. Like, what is the default LLM for our query engine? Right now, we'll be working with RAG, so our main discussion will be from query engine perspective.
Krish Naik: Then what is the embedding model that you want to use?
Krish Naik: default embedding model. Then comes, what is the chunk size, what is the chunk overlap, what type of splitting technique that you want to use. Okay, so here, split term is not used, you have to understand the other term, node parser.
Krish Naik: Because the core operation is parsing.
Krish Naik: Okay, so that's why they, work, or basically the name parse that comes here. Now, these are default settings, yes or no?
Krish Naik: like, global settings, I can say.
Krish Naik: Yes, everyone?
Krish Naik: Now, let's start doing the configuration. So, as I've imported settings, so directly through settings, I will be taking settings.llllm.
Krish Naik: The first setting, here I am passing OpenAI. Similarly, here I am passing the embed model, here I am passing the chunk size.
Krish Naik: Chunk overlap, and finally, defining my split mechanism through a, like, a segmental splitter. And here, these two parameters which have been defined, the chunk size and the chunk overlap, that I am taking. Okay, so let's try to print all the information.
Krish Naik: I hope this part is clear, nothing fancy.
Krish Naik: Simple, like, true settings. Always remember, you have to define your global settings that you want to use in the entire project.
Krish Naik: Now, let's start with, by bringing some document into the picture. So, right now, I'm using the default document class, just like in Lanshan also it is available.
Krish Naik: Okay, so here, I'm passing few amount of text, okay, and then I'm bringing some metadata.
Krish Naik: In Langdon, also, you had the same feature. There, it was context.
Krish Naik: And the metadata.
Krish Naik: So, right now, I have 3 different types of documents. So, let me load the documents. So, you can see, created 3 sample documents, and the total characters close to 1169.
Krish Naik: And now, like, the main object, like, source, category, majorly from the, metadata, if you look, everywhere I've taken intro, overview, embeddings, technical, and vector index, and technical topic, alright.
Krish Naik: Now, this document. So, I hope everybody understands document. I don't need to tell you about document.
Krish Naik: Because the same functionality is available in Langshan, so here also, where you'll be passing some context with the metadata. Now, for that document, if you want a specific ID, that also you can create some explicit IDs.
Krish Naik: Now, IDs will be important when?
Krish Naik: when it's a good practice to define an explicit ID? Can anybody tell me?
Krish Naik: Yes, anyone?
Krish Naik: when you are actually storing the information in VectorStore, everybody knows that for sure.
Krish Naik: But yes, I told you, like, metadata filtering. Similarly, like, on top of doc ID also, you can apply some type of filters.
Krish Naik: Okay, because in vector store, I can apply filters. Now the question comes, do you want to apply metadata filtering or dock ID filtering? So if you have some custom logic for your dock ID, then it is useful.
Krish Naik: Alright, now… So, let's start with our first index.
Krish Naik: Okay, so the first one that I'll be taking, so our three steps, chunking, Embedding and indexing.
Krish Naik: And right now, for indexing, I'll be using the in-memory default store. Okay, it means that the default vector store, which comes. In Langchain also, I've shown you the example of the inbuilt memory from Langchain, similarly. So here, I'm not using any third party.
Krish Naik: So, if you, look into the initialization, so, from vectors, like, vector store in text.
Krish Naik: From documents, then I'll be passing the set of documents here.
Krish Naik: Okay, and show progress is equal to true. Okay, alright.
Krish Naik: Now you will see that, okay, so through our text splitting, where we have defined the text sentence text splitter.
Krish Naik: Implications, so based on that, okay, the embeddings have been generated.
Krish Naik: Alright, and now I'm using in-memory. Okay, I'm not using any external BDV. Later on, I'll be showing you the integrations with Chroma, Quadrant, and with few other vector databases.
Krish Naik: Now, if I really say that, when you look into, like, from documents, is this syntax similar to LanChain? Yes or no?
Krish Naik: In Langshan also, very similar syntax you had, if you remember. See, like…
Krish Naik: If you are doing practice, you will remember the syntax. If you don't do practice, you will never remember the syntax.
Krish Naik: Always remember that, so it means that at least twice or thrice, if you execute the material that I have shared, then you will remember. So here, also, a very similar implementation, like fromDocs.com.
Krish Naik: Now, really, like, when I directly called, here, the vector, I can say the store index. So, what are the steps that, one by one, that has taken place? So, first of all, the document definition, where we have passed, each document was split into smaller chunks.
Krish Naik: Now, for splitting mechanism, which algorithm we used? We used sentence text splitter.
Krish Naik: Then, once we have those chunks, so chunks are referred to as node.
Krish Naik: In Llama Index, chunks are referred to as nodes.
Krish Naik: Okay, so when I say that, okay, find me the top K chance. So here, what we will call it?
Krish Naik: TopK nodes.
Krish Naik: Okay, always remember this, nodes, so…
Krish Naik: Chunk and note, same thing. Here, we don't use the term chunks a lot.
Krish Naik: Now, each node was embedded using OpenAI API, and then finally, once the embeddings are available, then vectors were stored in the simple vector store. So now, this simple vector store is an in-memory vector TV, which is available from Lama Index.
Krish Naik: There are different types of indexes. Later on that we'll be talking about, but for now, the most similar one.
Krish Naik: Now, let's start with a query.
Krish Naik: Now, this is the part where you pass your query.
Krish Naik: After indexing, I can say that my data ingestion phase is done. So, the next step that comes is that your query mechanism
Krish Naik: Where you'll be getting the results from your retriever.
Krish Naik: So, right now… As I have passed here index as query engine, so here I'm telling similarity top.
Krish Naik: Similarity top means that I am applying O-sign similarity. Based on that, I want to get my result. And here, there are different types of response mode. So, initially, we are starting with compact, but later on, I'll be showing you. Like, tree summarizer is there. Okay, really, a list of more than, I think, 5 to 6 are there.
Krish Naik: Now, based on that, your output changes. So, here I'm looking for small results, so that's why compact. It really works good with general documents.
Krish Naik: But if you have a complex structure, if you need a big, big, like, a very big response from the LLM, okay, then that, tree option is there. So I'll be talking about these features, but for now, Compact gives you, like, small answers, not very, very long.
Krish Naik: So, first of all, I'm just performing a…
Krish Naik: I can say cosine similarity search on top of our vector score index, and then, based on that, I'll be getting the, the small here.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: So right now, based on the response mode that I have, which is, like, top K is equal to 2,
Krish Naik: All right.
Krish Naik: Now, let's try to work with some queries.
Krish Naik: So, first of all, I'm just passing a new query.
Krish Naik: And this query engine that I've called.
Krish Naik: two types of engines are there in Lama Index, the chat engine and the query engine. In RAT, we'll be always using the query engine here. So right now, I'm just passing it, and based on that, just look for the response that you are getting.
Krish Naik: After the vector store index operation, next cell kernel crash.
Krish Naik: Like, really, like, how many of you are facing the issue of kernel crash? Rajat is mentioning?
Krish Naik: Mantaj is asking, we are not passing chunk… and chunk overlap.
Krish Naik: I've already defined it. Please go through the network at least once, I think. In my global settings, I have done the definition of these things.
Krish Naik: Please look into the code at least.
Krish Naik: Okay?
Krish Naik: Yes, see, if you're facing the issue, even, say, I face the issue, and generally.
Krish Naik: It can be, like, I failed the issue, then I actually deleted my environment and recreate it once. Then it started working for me. Last night, I failed the issue of kernel crash.
Krish Naik: Okay, and I think, probably some, the issue comes due to some C++ build. Okay, so just try to restart the condon and just have a check.
Krish Naik: Okay? Because only, I think, one is getting the issue of kernel crash.
Krish Naik: Alright, so now let's get back. I will start querying now.
Krish Naik: So, the first query I passed, what is LAMAIntex used for, and based on that, the response that I'm getting. So, lama index as a data framework, okay. Now, this is as per the document, the information that I have kept.
Krish Naik: So, really, if you want to look into the document, please go above, or copy some part.
Krish Naik: From here, and let's go to our actual document definition.
Krish Naik: So, here, if you look into Lama Index as a data framework for large language models, they provide tools. So, from here, they are actually getting the information.
Krish Naik: Look… Now, basic query.
Krish Naik: Alright… Now, let's try to analyze the response. It means that from which
Krish Naik: retrieval, like, from which chunk actually the information is coming. As I told you, like, you will be looking into the top K, whatever the results, so here I'll be looking into the top K nodes. That's why response.source notes.
Krish Naik: Source notes refers to those, top keychards that comes. Okay, and based on that, here, by default, you'll be always getting the score. What is the score?
Krish Naik: What is the score, guys?
Krish Naik: Same thing happens in Langen also. What type of score it will be? The similarity score, correct?
Krish Naik: Alright, now, if you, really look, so here, the similarity score is coming here, the 0.75, and if you really look into the content, I can say that, yes, this is the actual content from which it is coming. Similarly, for, source node 2, this is having lower similarity.
Krish Naik: But, the vector store index, because the term Llama Index has been used, so for sure, because of that, it has been given much higher priority, I can say.
Krish Naik: Okay, because the question was from Lama Index Prospect, and the appearance of the, word, I can say the token Llama Index was here. But, yes.
Krish Naik: Now, just tell me, like, when you looked into this temple, how many of you felt that it is easier than Lang Chen, or tougher than Lan Chen?
Krish Naik: Because I will take one survey, because for our future classes, which framework we want to stick to.
Krish Naik: Okay, probably when I'm showing you the implementations for Heidi, if I want to show you the implementations for re-ranking, okay, like, which framework you guys want, whether to go with Langchen or Llama Index.
Krish Naik: Okay, so…
Krish Naik: like, you guys can let me know, so based on that only I'll be picking up the implementations.
Krish Naik: My main preference will be Llama Index, but again, I will take a poll, and based on that poll only, I will say. Because Llama Index is for advanced users.
Krish Naik: Whichever is… there is nothing called as whichever. Both can be worked with Rishi. Okay, so it's totally up to you choice. I will raise a poll, and based on that pool.
Krish Naik: I will take the response.
Krish Naik: Alright, now analyzing the responses, alright.
Krish Naik: Now, similarity scores, okay. Now, let's, look into, some different types of queries, because we have queries from vector store related also. So, let's try to print the information here.
Krish Naik: So, right now, I'm not looking into the notes, but if you really look into how do embeddings works in Lama Index.
Krish Naik: Okay, the category is coming to technical, okay, and embedding. So, this is probably with, semantic meaning and numeric representation. So, if you really look into the document.
Krish Naik: Vector store index…
Krish Naik: So, this is the actual document, I can say, from where the information is coming related to your document indexing.
Krish Naik: Alright.
Krish Naik: So, first of all, let's pick up…
Krish Naik: Now, based on this, my idea will be you guys will be creating a tag. Okay, that will be a work that I'll be giving you.
Krish Naik: For your next week. Because the NEVRAG implementation that you have already looked into, a very similar implementation that you need to pick up for Lama Index, the same thing that we have done in the project. You need to do a reputation and a very similar implementation, but few things that I'll be changing.
Krish Naik: Right now, what is RAG? This is, I think, another query that we have for this. We already had the information.
Krish Naik: Okay, now let's try to look into the notes. Okay, so understanding the document, if you understand any document, you have to look into the node, and then text flow. Okay, so here, what do you mean by node? I hope everybody, first document, then chunks.
Krish Naik: Okay, and this index flow when I'm talking about, okay, now this is actually the information within your chance flow, how the flow of the nodes that comes.
Krish Naik: Like, in… I can say that, when you are actually placing the chunk, so based on what criteria that you'll be placing them.
Krish Naik: Now, passing the documents into notes manually to understand the flow, so let's try to get… so here I am using the most simplest form of center splitting. Chunk side 1024 with a chunk overlap, again, the definition.
Krish Naik: And now I'm not picking up anything from the global settings. Here you can see the manual. I have passed these params, or you can keep it in your global settings.
Krish Naik: Now, the number of nodes created here, so let's just look into. So, here, if you really look into the, node information, so right now, my main focus is towards the chunks.
Krish Naik: So, the first chunk, this is the chunk ID, or node ID, we call it here.
Krish Naik: Okay, then you have the character level information, then you have the metadata, and then you have these relationships. Okay, so for example, node relationship, the… it's coming from source 1.
Krish Naik: Okay? Then, again, the next relationship there, again, source 1 is there. I can see the related node info.
Krish Naik: So, here, if you look into, this is a different node, and this is a different node.
Krish Naik: It means that, can you define some relationship in between the nodes?
Krish Naik: Please let me know.
Krish Naik: Is it possible?
Krish Naik: Related… see, it means that, do you want to create some type of relationship between your channel? It's very, very important.
Krish Naik: Like, when I'll be talking from semantic chunking perspective, okay, so there, actually, this concept will come.
Krish Naik: Probably, like, if you have your entire data, okay, so there also you apply a sentence spreader, but on top of that, you calculate the emittings, and based on similarity, you try to group the sentences.
Krish Naik: But, like, can you create some type of relationship within those charms? So I feel that creating a relationship among the charms is always useful.
Krish Naik: Probably, like, from the score here.
Krish Naik: Directly I cannot decode, but if there is a relationship which has been defined, like chunk 1 is somehow related to chunk 3, or chunk 3 is somehow related to chunk 10, okay, in that way, you can create relationships here.
Krish Naik: Alright, now… Mood relationships, so parent and child.
Krish Naik: Relationships, very, very important. Now, parent and child structure. In chunking, much more of this information will come, because right now I've not told you about advanced chunking, but I will just tell you one scenario. Let's get back to notes.
Krish Naik: Let's take our advanced, I think, like, advanced able… here.
Krish Naik: So, let's take our… Semantic chanting.
Krish Naik: For now, I'll just give you an intuition. I'm not teaching it, so that you guys understand it here, okay? So, you have your document.
Krish Naik: Now, these documents will be broken into sentences.
Krish Naik: Okay, once the sentences are available, you will be calculating the embeddings.
Krish Naik: for every sentence. So, like, this is a much costlier operation, because you'll be performing that embedding operation.
Krish Naik: Okay, and then you will compare how similar they are. If they are not similar, simply you will not keep it. So once the embeddings are available, from here I will be getting the similarity.
Krish Naik: Among the sentences.
Krish Naik: Now, the next step that comes is grouping up those sentences with high similarity.
Krish Naik: If something is having lower similarity score, you can directly reject them or keep it, rejecting means that you will be keeping them in some other chunk. Now, this is one high-level intuition that I have provided.
Krish Naik: Now, coming to, child and parent relationship. So, in advanced chunking, when I'll be talking, so first of all, let's…
Krish Naik: Keep your context.
Krish Naik: In New York?
Krish Naik: parent.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: And all. So this is the actual context which your parents have, then you have multiple child.
Krish Naik: Child 1… Child 2…
Krish Naik: Child 3. So, this child that I'm referring, so these I am referring as chunks for now.
Krish Naik: Okay, it means that a hierarchical structure that I'll be defining. It means that the parent will be the main context saver.
Krish Naik: who will keep a very long context. Generally, like, the context for the parent, it can be very, very long.
Krish Naik: Okay, so the main context saver will be the parent, but for the, parent, there will be multiple child, and this I am referring as chunks here.
Krish Naik: All the childs are referred to chunks. So, generally, what happens, when you are applying embedding, these informations that we will be sending to VectorTV, we won't apply embedding on top of your parent.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: So, generally you can define a hierarchical structure. Okay, similarly, like, 3 levels of, structuring also we can do.
Krish Naik: But for now, this is the main idea. It means that you always look into the main context. So, during your retrieval, directly, I can look into these patterns. Like, here, directly on top of this, I can apply.
Krish Naik: But later on, because there is a linkage, or a relationship with the parent, so you can do a verification with the parent context also.
Krish Naik: Parent context, you really don't need to save it, otherwise you can keep it in VectorTV also. Like, for every child, as a separate metadata, you can keep the parent information.
Krish Naik: But I feel that the parent information is really… you don't need to see it. During runtime also, you can apply some type of, like, here you can apply text-based mechanisms.
Krish Naik: Okay, rather than vector-based operations.
Krish Naik: Okay, so we hear, algorithms like VM25, BM42, those things will come into the picture.
Krish Naik: How is the parent context created? We get it from the document only.
Krish Naik: We don't create anything. Everything is available in the document.
Krish Naik: Yes, correct context can be used as evaluation, correct intuition. Motaza.
Krish Naik: Generally, you don't need to keep your full document. Why you'll be keeping your full document? The parent should have context very similar to the chance.
Krish Naik: These things next week I'll be talking about, but are just a simple idea, because in Langchain, directly, these relationships are not available.
Krish Naik: Alright, let's get back, I think, my desktop.
Krish Naik: Kari?
Krish Naik: So, here, few node-based relationships based on chunks, okay, like source, link to the… this is the actual, by default, you get the source, then comes previous and next. It means that chunks can have sequential orders, and generally, the order comes from hierarchical structure only.
Krish Naik: Then, looking into the similarity top K results, impact on top K on the responses, so here you can play with this, because this is a simple hyperparameter to get the top K chance.
Krish Naik: Alright.
Krish Naik: Now, let's look into some response modes. Now, this is interesting. This is not available in LangChain.
Krish Naik: I feel that, that's why I love this. It means that the output, how we were looking for.
Krish Naik: Compact, it means that a very small one. Then you have tree summarize, then you have simple summarize. Okay, again, the list is long. Right now, I've just shown you three. I think more than 6 are available.
Krish Naik: Okay, so right now, these are a few of the features, because in our later notebooks for Llama, that we'll be talking. So here, I'm just passing these modes one by one with a for loop, and based on that, I pass it to the query engine, and I'll be getting the test. So let's try to analyze the differences.
Krish Naik: Right now, if you really look into the actual information flow that I have kept it here.
Krish Naik: You will see the output.
Krish Naik: So, first of all, hear that this functionality underpins RAC,
Krish Naik: you have to just focus on the last part. Okay, this functionality underpins rack. Okay, now if you really look into Compact and simple summarize. Compact means, again, a smaller version, I can say there. Okay, and this one, simple summarize.
Krish Naik: So somehow that summarization, the length is very, very similar for compact, but that tree summarized, it tries to give you a bigger response, so somehow they have increased the size of the response.
Krish Naik: And generally, like, when I'll be taking PDFs or some bigger documents, right now the size of the documents I'm working with very small, then I'll be, again, showing you. Most of the times, tree summarize is responsible if you're looking for bigger responses.
Krish Naik: Now, here, different type of response modes that I have taken, like Compact, which does the chunk concatenation and refines iteratively best for, like, your balanced quality and speed. Like, by default, everybody uses compact.
Krish Naik: Now comes your tree summarize, builds, summarize tree hierarchy, large context, comprehensive answers. Like, if you're really looking for
Krish Naik: Big, big answers, really, the flu. It feels that with a lot of context, if you feel that probably you might need 10 to 20 chunks, okay, for your context.
Krish Naik: To get your entire answer. In those cases, like, tree summarize is better. Then you have simple summarize, common one. Then you have refinement, iterably refine the answer with each chunk, where you want high-quality answers, but the speed will be very slow.
Krish Naik: Then you have accumulate, generate, separate, and serve per chunk.
Krish Naik: Okay, like, per chunk-wise, you can get the answer. So, through that operation, you can get multiple perspective also. Now, really, these features are powerful.
Krish Naik: And these are totally missing in Langshan. How many of you agree with this?
Krish Naik: In LanChain, if you want to do a modification, what you can do? All these things which are provided as features where you can add them.
Krish Naik: Just think and let me know. If you want a very similar type of implementation.
Krish Naik: what you can do. Only one option is there, imprompt.
Krish Naik: Yes, in-chain means in-chain, most of the things are static. Only one thing that can be changed, that is the prompt. Within the prompt, you,
Krish Naik: Like, you have to pass them. Okay, so that's why I feel that, like,
Krish Naik: for advanced users, like, see, even from my experience, I have worked much more with Langchain, but I feel that the Llama Index community has really taken a good turn.
Krish Naik: In 2024, the… I can say the development was somehow slower, but now it's really, really good.
Krish Naik: Okay, so why is Lama Index not so popular? Who told Lama Index it's not popular?
Krish Naik: Like, I don't know, how many of you have looked into the GitHub of Plama Index? How many stars are there?
Krish Naik: Yes, how many staff are there in Lama Index?
Krish Naik: Can you look into the stars as 45.9K, and if you look into LanChain, Anxion also has higher scarves.
Krish Naik: But I feel this will be somehow worse.
Krish Naik: Okay, now 122K.
Krish Naik: Now, really, when you look into why Langchain, LangChain is easy.
Krish Naik: But if you need, if you are a power user, I feel that Llama is better.
Krish Naik: Okay? So, yes, it is used in production. And generally, for parsing mechanisms, I do love Llama parse alone.
Krish Naik: in, like, client projects I've used.
Krish Naik: Now, let's get back. Okay, so here. So, this is the first notebook, to help you get started. Then I'll be picking up the next notebook, where some more advanced topics. Now, just tell me, like, here, the first thing, just tell me, like, with respect to prompts, have you worked anything?
Krish Naik: Tell now, anything from the prompt, respect, Have I done anything?
Krish Naik: Yes or no?
Krish Naik: Nothing, because I've not worked with prompts. And I can say, see, really, like, I know that internally, when I use different, response engines, okay, so here, the different modes. I know internally, behind the scenes, they are using some prompt.
Krish Naik: Directly not, but I know that, yes, if you want to get output in this way, you have to define some type of prompt.
Krish Naik: Look, generic prom draft, they have kept it.
Krish Naik: Now, let's move to our next notebook.
Krish Naik: I think the next notebook is from the document prospect.
Krish Naik: Hmm, and do a save.
Krish Naik: How we can concurinate all chunks in PROM, just by passing… first of all, Amit, why you want to concurinate all chunks?
Krish Naik: Okay, like, you were telling about that particular IDC. Generally, there it will be coming, but before that concatenation, you perform a join operation. If you… how many of you remember that format? Dev, helper format?
Krish Naik: There you do the concatenation, where you use that join, and each chunk on top of that you apply.
Krish Naik: So you have to pass it through some type of function as a placeholder.
Krish Naik: Okay, I mean, it means that within a variable, you'll be saving all the chunk information, and that chunk, you have to pass it as a placeholder within the prompt, so that it gets recognized.
Krish Naik: I hope you get returned.
Krish Naik: Alright, now let's try to look into some more advanced features, so here I'll be taking some data.
Krish Naik: I think in my data, in my research papers… okay, I have few papers at least.
Krish Naik: But, similarly, you can take a PDF and just, keep it inside the research paper folder.
Krish Naik: I… I don't think I have shared the, research papers with you. Please have a check, even I don't…
Krish Naik: I remember in the data, do I have…
Krish Naik: research papers… no, I have not provided the research papers, only the folder structure I have provided. Please check
Krish Naik: Okay, and then just keep a PDF there for now.
Krish Naik: Try to take a small PDF, if you're working with OpenAI, really, so many pages we don't want, take a simple PDF and keep it there.
Krish Naik: Again, Reva is asking, please share the repo link.
Krish Naik: Like, guys, I've already shared the Ripple link so many times, it's better to keep it in Notion.
Krish Naik: People joining late.
Krish Naik: Alright, I appreciate it.
Krish Naik: please keep a PDF in the research paper folders, okay? I hope you guys will be having some PDF, or keep… attention is all you need, something like that.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, coming to the implementations for the Lama Intexpore.
Krish Naik: So, first of all, I'm getting a vector store index, a simple directory reader, settings document, and the last time also I've done, similar calls.
Krish Naik: Then, lama index score schema. So, from here, text node, node relationship, and related node info. In this notebook, I want to focus on these topics a little bit, okay?
Krish Naik: Then comes, different type of, parsers which are available, from chunking strategies. Let's try to do a comparison. So, for that, I have taken sentence splitter. Then the last notebook, I have taken that. Then comes token text splitter. So, if you want to apply token splitting splitting mechanism, token refers to a simple word.
Krish Naik: Then comes your semantic splitter. Now, this implementation is also available here, but remember, semantic splitter is a costly operation, because for every sentence, your embeddings will be calculated. It means that your OpenAI embedding model will be used.
Krish Naik: So, please take a small PDF, okay? Then again, otherwise, you will be charged, you will, like, your credits will be exhausted.
Krish Naik: Then comes metadata extraction. So, to work with metadata, here, there are two types of extractors, the title extractor and the summary extractor that you have.
Krish Naik: Okay, now,
Krish Naik: If you really look into the features now, these are the actual features that we work in production, directly, and these features are directly available here. Then you have an ingestion pipeline. I really, really love this implementation of ingestion pipeline.
Krish Naik: In Llama. Directly, I'll be showing you, through a pipeline, you can just pass, okay? This is my LLM, this is my embedding model, these are my vectors, this is my checking strategy done. Just keep it in one pipeline, and execute it. Really easy to work with.
Krish Naik: Then you have your LLM and embedding settings, just like last time, and the other imports are fine, so let me just re-execute.
Krish Naik: this notebook.
Krish Naik: See, like, if you don't have credits, you need to load it up.
Krish Naik: Can we take a break? I can take a break. It's 10.20. Do you want… do you guys want a 10-minute break?
Krish Naik: Or, like, after discussing few things.
Krish Naik: break.
Krish Naik: Attention is all you need is small. No, no, no, no, attention is all you need. I think it has close to 19 pages, or something like that. Take a smaller PDF, because there is a semantic chunking. I don't want your OpenAI credits to be exhausted.
Krish Naik: Alright, let's take a break. Okay, I'll be back then. Yes, like, small PDF, 3 pages, 2 pages, and that way.
Krish Naik: In my case, also, I've taken a small one. Alright, let me start the timer, okay?
Krish Naik: Alright, 10 minutes break or 15 minutes break, 10.45 around.
Krish Naik: Okay, people are telling 15 minutes. Fine, I'll be back in 15, even I will do my breakfast.
Krish Naik: Let's take the clock, okay.
Krish Naik: Alright, so I'll be back after my breakfast.
Krish Naik: Yes, they have Ulama integration, don't worry, I'll be talking about those things.
Krish Naik: Alright guys, so let's continue our discussion.
Krish Naik: If you don't have a PDF, it's fine. We do have a sample document, you can use that for now.
Krish Naik: Alright, so let's start.
Krish Naik: The first part, the imports, was working fine, then the next part is setting
Krish Naik: From the global settings, so I'm just using settings.lllm and embedding model, two things that I have taken, and the model dimension that we have passed it here.
Krish Naik: Okay, so now the settings are configured.
Krish Naik: So, let's move. So, here, like, if you have anything, I think, in my case, I do have two PDFs related to brain tumor.
Krish Naik: Okay, in your case, if there are PDFs, it will be shown.
Krish Naik: Otherwise, the sample document is there, you can work with that, using the default document class of Lama Index.
Krish Naik: Now, when you look into the simple directory features, I want to just tell you, like, which are the features which are available. This is better than the LandChain directory reader, I feel, somehow. So, what are the different type of extensions that you can work with? It will do a recursive scan also, if you have subdirectories in those cases.
Krish Naik: Fileenames has document IDs that can be created.
Krish Naik: Okay, now this is really good.
Krish Naik: Otherwise, manually, in metadata, we can save it. Then comes file metadata, like, you can add custom metadata, also, like, you can pass through it, I will show you. Exclude hidden, skip hidden files. So, the features are better as compared to land sharing files.
Krish Naik: Now, this is a sample document where we have some amount of text and some amount of metadata. Okay, so one is related to attention is all you need, and the other one is related to birth, and the third one is related to the rag paper.
Krish Naik: Okay, so let me just execute.
Krish Naik: Okay, so 3 documents are now created.
Krish Naik: Now, let's look into the metadata, okay? Now, if you really look here, in sample papers, sample papers mean the documents that we have created. Then, within the metadata, I'm looking for, like, processed
Krish Naik: Data, character count, and word count.
Krish Naik: These informations that are coming right now.
Krish Naik: Okay, so… let me just show you. So, what are the changes? If you really look into the metadata.
Krish Naik: Now, okay, so title, author, year, category, these are the default ones that I have created. Now, manually, what I have injected.
Krish Naik: So, process date, so datetime.now, then come the length of the document text, and then finally the word count that we are getting. For the document, we are applying a split operation. So, can you see, like, manual injection of metadata?
Krish Naik: It means that manually you can perform an inject operation here.
Krish Naik: In Lanjan also, you have to do it manually, but I feel that it's much easier here.
Krish Naik: as compared to, Langshan, like, Llama Index directly, you can add this metadata.
Krish Naik: Okay, so it really helps you much easier. I hope everybody understood this part, what I have done, I have manually injected few metadata.
Krish Naik: Previously, if you look into the metadata.
Krish Naik: Title, authors, years, category in this way, but this time I've added a few more information, like percentage date, character count, and word count here.
Krish Naik: Please let me know.
Krish Naik: Please let me know, guys. Is this fine for everyone? Because this is the first time I'm showing you how to inject metadata.
Krish Naik: Where it will help, it will help you during your retrieval. All this type of information which you added in the metadata, it is helpful during your retrieval technique. It means that you can apply filters, as simple as that. If you can apply filters on your vector TV, that is the main purpose, so that you can get your results better.
Krish Naik: Can you show us an example, like, how metadata helps? Already shown, I think, there, in the… when I was discussing Quadrant, there I have applied filters, MS.
Krish Naik: For your referral.
Krish Naik: There is no assisted learning, it's just, on top of which you can apply filters, as simple as that. There is no learning mechanism here, if I'm adding metadata.
Krish Naik: Generally, in production, your metadata attributes will be very, very long, like at least 15 to 20 fibs, which are used.
Krish Naik: You will think about the schema for your metadata, few things that comes, but actually, like, regarding file type, what type of information, chunk info, chunk ID, document ID, these are a few common things which we, like, we always use.
Krish Naik: I think I have shown you examples related to metadata filtering. How many of you remember that in line chain? I think in Quadrant and the VVX section, when I discussed, I applied filters also.
Krish Naik: Yes?
Krish Naik: Is it good to put the chunk text here? You can put the chunk text. No issue.
Krish Naik: See, like, it doesn't create the complexity. Even in production, I keep the chunk text inside the metadata.
Krish Naik: Because I feel that why it is important, because those are actually embeddings. So really, if I want to go through what is the chunk and what is the text, so it helps me. So in the metadata, yes, I keep the entire chunk text there.
Krish Naik: Hmm?
Krish Naik: The metadata on top… see, metadata, you don't embed the information.
Krish Naik: Metadata information you want to be embedding.
Krish Naik: the next thing.
Krish Naik: I hope. You will be only, keeping your, vectors. The vectors are basically your chunk information that you will embed, but the metadata information you don't embed.
Krish Naik: But there is a technique where you, in some, papers I have seen, in some research papers, where people have done that also. Like, the metadata information also, they have kept it in the embedded.
Krish Naik: There is one technique, but few papers are there. It's not like a global implementation, everybody is doing that.
Krish Naik: Now, Nirut is asking, how do you keep chunk text and metadata? Anybody can do it, it's a simple operation. Like, within the dictionary, you have to just create a key, text, and what is the chunk information? Just pass it there.
Krish Naik: These are simple Pythonic parts.
Krish Naik: Okay? Alright.
Krish Naik: Now, let's start with the next part.
Krish Naik: Now, let's focus on, I think, three chunking strategies that we have defined in our notebook. So, the first one, which is the sentence-based chunking, and I think, in the next class, we'll be talking much more about advanced chunking strategies.
Krish Naik: But here, few options are there. Like, the sentence splitter is the default one. Like, in Langchain, everybody uses
Krish Naik: Which operation? The recursive text character splitter, if you remember.
Krish Naik: So here, very similar implementations are available, just the, I can say, the detour, line chain.
Krish Naik: So here, initially, we are starting with a sentence splitter.
Krish Naik: Then, we have defined here the chunk size, the chunk overlap, and right now the separator, you can see, pretty much blank. Okay, so split on spaces first. That is the priority.
Krish Naik: Now, send us Twitter.getNotes, so when I'm telling getNotes from document, so what it will do?
Krish Naik: Yes, what are notes in Lama Index? Quickly tell me, guys. Quickly write in chat.
Krish Naik: get notes from chunks, it means that chunking operation will take place. Okay, and here I am passing my set of documents, which is basically the sample papers. Okay, let's try to take a preview of the chunks.
Krish Naik: So, right now, if you look into the chunk, total number, the input documents that we had, and right now, the chunk size is 1024, okay? Now, this is really a big chunk size, and the size of the documents that we have passed is small only, it's not very big.
Krish Naik: So, I feel that, based on our chunking mechanism, total input documents are 3, the output nodes are 3. Average characters, you can look into 936. So, the chunk size was 1024. So, based on that, 3 documents, 3 chunks.
Krish Naik: So the first node preview, or basically the chunk preview that you have, the text, the information, okay, so this is the actual, text information that you had, and I'm just showing you the first 200 characters.
Krish Naik: then you have your main metadata. So, similarly, you can just look into your second one if you just change here the index.
Krish Naik: Okay, so the second was from the BERT paper, so here also we are looking into the starting 200 characters, and then we are looking into the metadata part.
Krish Naik: So, now this operation is very similar to Langchain, there is no such difference.
Krish Naik: Now, chunk size selection, so really, this is a hyperparameter I have already told you.
Krish Naik: Previously, you can always start with something medium. I love this range, working with medium, small chunks, not a fan, but again, it depends upon the data. If I'm working with, like, programming languages, then I can go with smaller chunks. I feel this is a safe size. But for general purpose text, I feel medium works really good.
Krish Naik: And large, I'm not really a fan of this one. Okay? I feel that 1024 is really a good number, below that, like, somewhere around 736 to 1024.
Krish Naik: Now, let's take another example, which is a token text splitter which is available.
Krish Naik: the very similar implementation here. Token means? What is the meaning of token?
Krish Naik: I hope everybody understands by this time.
Krish Naik: Token refers to, word, correct.
Krish Naik: Now, here, based on this particular implementation, okay, so the overlap, the chunk size that we have taken, you can see this time we have reduced.
Krish Naik: The chunk overlap is close to 128, now 25% overlap is here, so this is really big. I prefer somewhere around 20%.
Krish Naik: Okay, and again, the same number of operations, but let's try to look into all the characters, because here, what is the average characters that are coming? So here also, in the…
Krish Naik: Input documents, close to 3 documents that we have passed. Output nodes, 3, average characters, so the core information is pretty much same. I won't see any major changes here.
Krish Naik: Okay, so right now, I'm based on… so there are also 3 chunks, here also 3 chunks.
Krish Naik: Now, really, like, I have not taken the print operation, but if you want to really do the printing of that, I think you can take from this code, and you can print the information.
Krish Naik: Okay, so let's try to print it.
Krish Naik: So here, if I try to add a port cell, let me just bring this port.
Krish Naik: Text, okay, let me look into the variable. This is token notes, so this I need to update. Sentence to token.
Krish Naik: Okay, so token notes… I think the rest of the information will remain the same.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, if you really look into here, the starting 200 characters, and based on that, we are getting the information. So, if you really look into the token text splitter, which is even giving you 3 nodes, but the average character per node that you have is close to 936.
Krish Naik: Okay, now these are written in characters, not in tokens.
Krish Naik: Okay? SK for you.
Krish Naik: Please enter phone.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, based on that particular size, I can say that, yes, 936 characters are coming. So, based on that, our splitters are there, so 3 and 3 nodes are here.
Krish Naik: Alright, so, very similar results. Now, the main change, because now, from here, something new that will come. Token text splitter, please don't use it. It's just for the purpose of today's demo I'm showing, nobody uses token text letter.
Krish Naik: Sentencers are much better, because I know that most of the times your data will be much more complex.
Krish Naik: Now comes your semantic one. Now, this is really important. Now, what happens here? Here, embedding will take place. So, in the sentence splitter mechanism, you can see that I am passing an embedding model.
Krish Naik: What I told you in the notes also I have, told, first of all, you have your document. That document will be converted into text, and finally, the grouping will take place.
Krish Naik: Okay, do you want me just to take some examples and show you again? In the notes? Please let me know.
Krish Naik: If it is required, again, I will just do a quick recap.
Krish Naik: Okay, I will take some images this time, just wait, let me get some images.
Krish Naik: All right, so let's start, I will just get back to notes.
Krish Naik: desktop, iPad, wire cable.
Krish Naik: Alright, I think every one of you can see this one. So, quickly, let's take a piece of text, first of all.
Krish Naik: Okay. So, it really works good with the text.
Krish Naik: Okay, I will bring, and I will paste it here.
Krish Naik: what have happened to the notes, I think.
Krish Naik: my iPad… Alright.
Krish Naik: So, this is the right batch, or right here.
Krish Naik: No, this is coming, the other image.
Krish Naik: Just wait, let me have to take this few screenshots.
Krish Naik: Alright, I think this is fine now. Now, this is a piece of text. Now, on top of that, that text, you have to apply the splitting mechanism. The first step, on top of which you'll be applying your sentence-based text splitters. It means that every sentence, you will try to break it into a separate sentence.
Krish Naik: Okay, so here… No…
Krish Naik: Okay, if you really try to compare this image and this image, please look into exactly the…
Krish Naik: implementation that I have done. What I have done, simply, I can say, I can done the splitting on top of sentences.
Krish Naik: Now, for each sentence, you have to generate the embeddings. Always remember that. So, this is a costly operation.
Krish Naik: It means that you are paying some money, or if you are using an open source model, that is also fine. But…
Krish Naik: That… the next step that comes into the picture, which is creating the embeddings.
Krish Naik: So, every time going with semantic chunking is not a solution, I feel. For simple type of documents, it is not really, really important.
Krish Naik: Okay, for every sentence I am doing. And then finally, what I will do, I will group the sentences based on embedding similarity. Okay, and based on that, the chunks will be created.
Krish Naik: to… to the final approach. So, mainly four steps are there, but anybody has learned hierarchical clustering?
Krish Naik: in machine learning, because next week I'll be talking about that.
Krish Naik: When you try to, implement your custom semantic implementation.
Krish Naik: Because this is a direct available, but in the next class, I'll be showing you, like, manually how to create your custom semantic junker.
Krish Naik: Okay, now…
Krish Naik: So, how many steps are there? Load the data, break it into sentences, convert them into embeddings, calculate the similarity. Once the similarity is calculated, then you will group the sentences in a simple chunk.
Krish Naik: Okay? Please do remember that. This is the high-level idea. Like, okay, somebody told, tree-based clusters, like dendograms. Yes, that exactly comes in hierarchical clustering. Like, in the next class, I'll be showing you a manual implementation and how to do the visualization. If there are multiple types of outliers in your data, exactly how you can visualize those things.
Krish Naik: Can you zoom into chunk 1? So, really, I can't zoom, but yes.
Krish Naik: Okay, this is the same sentence that I have taken, later on broken into multiple sentences, then calculated the embeddings, and finally created the jumps.
Krish Naik: Okay, so here, grouping of sentences happens based on the embedding similarity.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: Now, let's get back to our implementation of semantic chunks.
Krish Naik: Did it combine the group of sentences? Yes.
Krish Naik: It will combine, no? Similar sentences will be grouped.
Krish Naik: Alright, now let's come back to our notes.
Krish Naik: In Langchain, can you do grouping of sentences? In Langchain also, there is a semantic text editor, which is available. So, there you can use it.
Krish Naik: Is it parent and child? No. Right now, no parent and child that I've told.
Krish Naik: Alright, now let's get back here. So, here, based on the implementations.
Krish Naik: So, the first one, one, like, buffer size is equal to 1 that I'm passing.
Krish Naik: Now, these are sentences to group for comparison.
Krish Naik: Then you have your breakpoint percentile threshold, which is 95, sensitive to semantic breaks. Now, this is very, very important. Now, this parameter should always be high.
Krish Naik: If at any point of time, if you feel that, okay, the similarity is going towards the lower side, okay, please do a break. It means that create a new chunk for that particular information. And then finally, you have that embedding model selection, which is really good.
Krish Naik: Ideally use an embedding slash an LLM to find the points where, there I'll be talking about, because in semantic chunking, the first topic that comes is your hierarchical clustering, then LLM-based clustering, Rahul. Okay?
Krish Naik: Alright, now, first of all.
Krish Naik: I'm not talking about advanced chunking, so don't ask me questions related to chunking now, because those topics I'll be covering. Here, just look into the implementation through Lama Index, okay? Because our next class agenda is only related to chunking.
Krish Naik: Okay, because right now, the entire topic of semantic chunking, I have not taught. Like, clustering will come, LLM-based, even agentic-based chunking, so those things will come in the next class. For now, just look into the implementation. There is no splitter which is best, MS. There is no such thing.
Krish Naik: Okay, if you're spending more money, I can say that, generally, like, LLM-based text printers are really good, but yes, it comes with a cost. Similarly for agentic-based chunking also.
Krish Naik: It always comes with a cost.
Krish Naik: Alright, so let's look into the implementation now.
Krish Naik: So right now, I have initialized my semantic splitter. Then, in the next step, I will be applying the chunks. Now, this time, you will see that the number of nodes will be different.
Krish Naik: Okay, so let's… as you know, this is an embedding API call, so this will take more time as compared to your other text letters.
Krish Naik: Okay, because, yes, there is, like, somebody's asking if you are using LLMs, is there a scenario of hallucination? Yes, for sure, there will be an issue with respect to hallucination.
Krish Naik: Okay. Like, yes, NLM-based tech splitters, that is one con that you have.
Krish Naik: Now, here, if you really look into, the number of input documents are 3, and the number of output nodes are 6.
Krish Naik: So, can I say that this time, really, like, when I applied semantic chunking, so based on that, really, the number of chunks.
Krish Naik: has changed, as compared to directly applying some rules. Here, I'm not applying any rules. Okay, like, I hope everybody understood the meaning of rules. It means that the separation would just take a white space. Okay, I would probably take a slash in, or take it, double, slash N, slash in two times.
Krish Naik: Okay, for a paragraph 3. I'm not taking those.
Krish Naik: Okay, so directly, I'm looking into the embeddings, the similarity.
Krish Naik: And based on that, I have taken.
Krish Naik: Yes, the 3 node becomes 6.
Krish Naik: Now, if you really want to print all the information, so let me just take this piece of code, the first note preview for this one.
Krish Naik: Okay, and let's take this one as… Thinks… the one thing.
Krish Naik: Nevermind.
Krish Naik: All right.
Krish Naik: Okay, so here I can say, initially, Okay…
Krish Naik: Because all the indexes using a for loop, you can actually look into that. But the core information is pretty much the same. I won't say there is a lot of changes, but in the first note, if you really look into… Okay, now this time, the first note, and this time, the first note, because this is here exactly the start of the document.
Krish Naik: if… Just check here.
Krish Naik: This is the start of the document that you have, title, authors, year, okay, and then actually your abstract, which is actually defined in your original document.
Krish Naik: Okay, so this is how the original document looked like. Title, author. So you can see that, okay, from the starting point, it is coming. Can you see here?
Krish Naik: Now, when I'm working with semantic.
Krish Naik: Okay, this time, the first node preview has changed.
Krish Naik: Can I say that?
Krish Naik: Because I have, alright, let me just make it zero for now. I'm looking into the second index, but I think it will be… should be somehow similar.
Krish Naik: But, something with respect to the abstract, the dominant sequence here also, it is coming.
Krish Naik: And if you try to, take the other version of this one.
Krish Naik: From semantic chunks, let me just take the
Krish Naik: First node, okay. Let's look into the first node only.
Krish Naik: Okay, and let's try to compare both.
Krish Naik: So here, if you really look into, I feel the results are very, very similar. Okay, now, actually, but the number of, chunks have increased. For our initial,
Krish Naik: chunk, I can see the starting point is same, but if you really want to look into… because I know that my main document has been divided into two more parts, so really, I can look into chunk 1 and chunk
Krish Naik: One, okay.
Krish Naik: To understand the difference.
Krish Naik: So, this chunk that you have, I can say this is different.
Krish Naik: Because this chunk is related to attention is all you need. But in the other implementation, here, if you have looked into your chunk one, it was directly from birth. So I can say that my first information, or the first document, has been broken into two parts, based on that similarity score calculation.
Krish Naik: Yes or no, because…
Krish Naik: Totally, the information is different here. For this chunk, which is the first index, 0th index, the same information, but at least for the second index, we are getting a different one.
Krish Naik: Now, with semantic chunking, I feel that semantic chunking is good, but, every time working with semantic chunking, again, like, whenever you are working with semantic chunks, it's a good practice to go with lower chunk size and, lower chunk overlap.
Krish Naik: never pass big chunk size or big, overlapping values. It's a bad practice.
Krish Naik: Deepug is asking which line in Python does the grouping of sentences? You have to write your own line of code for that debug.
Krish Naik: Alright.
Krish Naik: Now, let's take that one.
Krish Naik: Share the preview code, which preview code you require?
Krish Naik: Because, really, there is no such,
Krish Naik: I think everybody can take this preview code, you can write it by yourself, you have to just change the name of the variable, which is basically the node representation, the node variable. You guys can do it, yes, fine.
Krish Naik: Now, see, semantic chunking advantages, really like this, but…
Krish Naik: But let's go in high level. Embedding the consecutive sentences. So, you can see, during the embedding, really, it will pick up, calculate the cosine similarity between the embeddings.
Krish Naik: splits where the similarity drops. Now, this is the topic change, but again, like, topic detection is another level. It means that
Krish Naik: There is a concept of topic shift detection. Anybody else heard about that topic?
Krish Naik: like, really, like, topic shift detection. It's, again, for advanced…
Krish Naik: implementations, where you actually check that, does the context are really the same between the…
Krish Naik: I can say, the chunks.
Krish Naik: If it is totally different, directly we'll drop. Anybody has heard about topic?
Krish Naik: Detection, not hot. Alright, fine, leave those.
Krish Naik: Now, comes to the pros, preserve the semantic coherence. So, for sure, semantic coherence has to be there, as you are working with cosine similarity. Natural topic boundaries, it respects, it's good, it works good for complex documents.
Krish Naik: Alright, now coming to the comms, LU requires embedding API calls, variable chunk sizes, higher cost, more API calls. So, best for academic papers, technical docs, and long form of content.
Krish Naik: So, my first choice is not always semantic, really. Like, if your document is complex, then only always try to use. Otherwise, take some other type of simpler approaches.
Krish Naik: Now, let's try to do a comparison directly on top. Okay, now this is a simple dictionary that I have created, and I'll be applying the for loop. And based on that, my sentence notes, token notes, and semantic nodes are already available. So on top of that, let's look into the comparison part.
Krish Naik: So, previously I've shown you the results directly, but in one place right now.
Krish Naik: The major difference comes from semantic. If you really look into semantic, the average characters have decreased, the minimum characters have decreased, the maximum characters have decreased.
Krish Naik: Okay, and the standard deviation, if you really look into this as increased.
Krish Naik: Okay, now, when you actually try to compare it with any other rule-based chunking mechanism.
Krish Naik: I feel that, like, semantic is really far in. It means that everything you need to be dependent on an embedding model. Just think about, if you don't have a good embedding model, then what will happen?
Krish Naik: Because the first dependency is creating good embeddings. If you have bad embeddings, what… can I say that a direct impact to my chunking strategy? Really doesn't matter whether it works or not.
Krish Naik: Yes? So, like, that's why I feel this is a risky business. It means that you have to spend a lot on embedding. First of all, like, to do the chunking, you will spend on embedding.
Krish Naik: to do your main operation, which is the actual embedding, the vector index operation, there also you'll be spending money. Just remember, if you're going with the strategies, your initial cost will always rise.
Krish Naik: Semantic checking happens only within the same docs, or based on similarity. It happens within the same docs, for sure, it will happen within the same doc. If it is the same document, within that you have the sentences. On top of the sentences, it is applied mind.
Krish Naik: Okay? Similarly, for your other document, if you have two PDFs, the approach will be the same.
Krish Naik: All right, now let's jump into the strategies.
Krish Naik: Yes, the first node will be the same. Check in the second node.
Krish Naik: Now, let's look into metadata management, adding custom node-level metadata. So, let's see. Now, node-level metadata means chunk-level metadata. Now, this is the actual thing that even we do with Langchen, a very similar implementation here also.
Krish Naik: Now, for I, comma node in, okay, on top of sentence notes that I have taken. Okay, so sentence notes.
Krish Naik: Here, the first strategy that I've taken here is node.metadata, node index. So here, I am iterating on top of i. It means that it will keep on iterating.
Krish Naik: Then comes node.metadata, chunk strategy, and here I am passing sentence. So, like, in your metadata, do you want to save the information, how you have done the chunking?
Krish Naik: I hope you are getting.
Krish Naik: this information. Because, like, just think I have done my work, and later on, I leave the organization, and later on, somebody comes.
Krish Naik: You really need to look into the source code, but directly through metadata, if you save this type of information, it becomes much better to collaborate with others also. So, try to keep such information which helps you. If you want to change directly some strategy, these things can be done.
Krish Naik: Then, two information that I have added now, the node index and the chunk strategy. Now, derive the metadata from the main context, okay, so first of all, I'm taking the main information, node.txt means chunk.
Krish Naik: The actual, on top of that, I am performing a lower operation. Now, node.metadata now has abstract, like, now I'm looking for a very specific keyword in text.lua. Similarly, has introduction, mention, transformers, in. Now, these are certain conditions, and based on that, are you printing the information?
Krish Naik: Now, few information, like title, authors, year, category, citations…
Krish Naik: source. Okay, then comes your, like, process date.
Krish Naik: character count, word count, then comes your node index. This information, previously, I have added, till word count, if you remember. Last time I showed you how to add that metadata. After this, you need to focus on. What is the node index right now?
Krish Naik: 0th one. Right now, I'm looking into the first only, so that's why zeroth index that I have picked. Now, look into the chunking strategy. I've added manually another level of metadata. Here, I'm telling that, okay, central splitter that I have used.
Krish Naik: as abstract.
Krish Naik: True. It means that I'm applying some type of logic to check within the text, because once it is converted into embedding, nothing I can do.
Krish Naik: I know that there are only numbers, and really, numbers from numbers, I cannot make any type of meaning, or to make any type of logic. But directly, on top of this, that I have kept, even sometimes we keep phrases also.
Krish Naik: So right now, has the abstract true, has the introduction true, and mention transformers true. Can you see subtle logic that I have developed?
Krish Naik: Based on some conditions. It might be useful, I don't know, but for now, the poor idea was to show you that, yes. So, just tell me, if you have this metadata, and if you try to look for abstract for a certain paper, okay, can you directly look into this chunk? Yes, sir.
Krish Naik: Because this chunk has the information about abstract. So during your metadata filtering on top of the VDB, like quadrant, just apply a filter.
Krish Naik: So it becomes much easier at any point of time.
Krish Naik: Let's move ahead with LLM-based metadata extraction. Now, again, now, this is a costly technique.
Krish Naik: I feel that till now, there is no library, directly for metadata. Anybody has worked with a library which is purely built for metadata. Till now, I have not worked, so I'm asking anybody if you have worked with such a library.
Krish Naik: Let me know, let me know. Anybody?
Krish Naik: has worked with any metadata library.
Krish Naik: for Gen AI frameworks, because many of you are working
Krish Naik: Nobody has done it, simply say a no in the chat, at least.
Krish Naik: Not done? Alright.
Krish Naik: Fine. Then, see, because I was planning to do something like, okay, so if… then probably, like, next year, I will take a bowl. If somebody's interested in doing the development.
Krish Naik: Okay, so I will only pick up specific students with whom I know they are good, with backend. Okay, so if few people are interested, you can let me know. Then, probably in this course, we can create a library, okay, at least. Then, because few things that needs to be taken care of.
Krish Naik: The chunking, chunking, and indexing.
Krish Naik: And, we'll be working with at least 10 to 15 major vector databases, so in that way, I can plan.
Krish Naik: It's not about anybody can join, at least I need to check your… Level.
Krish Naik: of coding, because when I give you one task, I know few people can do it, but not everyone. You use vibe coding, I have no issues, but at least the core logic and the concept should be great. Okay, so probably next year, just give me a reminder, then we can start working on a very specific framework, just to work with metadata.
Krish Naik: So that anybody can bring Langchain, and based on that, some type of schema definition we need to take care of, okay, and based on that, we can do. Now, LLM-based metadata extraction, really, again, are costly.
Krish Naik: technique, but as you can see here, to information that I'm taking the title extractor. Now, if you remember, in our text, very specifically, the title content was written.
Krish Naik: Okay, then comes your summary and title-based. So, first of all, I'm just initializing the title extractor, then comes your summary extractor, the implementations that I have taken.
Krish Naik: So, first of all, in both the places, the LLM definition, max number of nodes, okay, let's look into the first 5 nodes, just like in head operation, in Pandas.
Krish Naik: Then, coming to the summaries. Now, here you'll be getting the summaries, so summarize each notice. That's why this particular parameter comes as self.
Krish Naik: So, let's take this one, and let's look into exactly how it looks like. So, first of all, I will apply this. This is the initialization. In the next step, sample nodes for extraction.
Krish Naik: And here, I'm passing my sentence note. So, sentence notes, previously, this information was saved. So, if you really forgot about sentence notes, just try to take a print here. I will take the sentence notes.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: Because you might forget the variables, just to show you. Okay, so what is their main chunks, I can say.
Krish Naik: Which was done using the sentence, splitter.
Krish Naik: Now, here I'm just passing
Krish Naik: Okay, it is 0 syntax, I think 3 documents are there, so 0, 1, 2.
Krish Naik: Then comes your, extract summaries. Okay, so here I am applying, first of all, the summary extractor.
Krish Naik: Okay, and then processing the nodes, it means that process the chunks, and then finally, you need to pass the data on top of which you'll be applying. So here, sample nodes for extraction, so this is the chunk-level data that I am passing.
Krish Naik: Tehan, let's see, first of all, like, how we are getting the results.
Krish Naik: Okay, this will take some time, so just wait.
Krish Naik: So that's why, don't work with big documents, because in this particular notebook, for every type of operation, it costs
Krish Naik: Okay, so please use smaller documents, or use at least the one that I have taken.
Krish Naik: Mmm.
Krish Naik: Alright, now…
Krish Naik: Just check the integrations with us, if open metadata, as you were telling, addresses the need for your metadata, but check the integrations with major frameworks are there on.
Krish Naik: If it is there, then we can tick it.
Krish Naik: Alright, now if I'm looking into the extracted summaries, okay, so just look into the summary part. Now, this is the actual metadata information that you will be saving.
Krish Naik: Now, in the summary, if you look, this section discusses the research paper.
Krish Naik: ballright, titled Attention is All You Need, authored by this information. It introduces the transformer's architecture, which is a noble approach to sequence transaction that relies entirely on attention mechanisms. Okay.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, this is a summary which has been generated by the LLM.
Krish Naik: And now this information, do you feel that, is it important?
Krish Naik: How many of you think that it is important?
Krish Naik: Okay, so, one thing I will tell you, like, this information is also important. Why?
Krish Naik: I have seen in few approaches, okay, where actually this summarized information is converted into embeddings. And on top of that, also, you might do a very similarity score.
Krish Naik: just to have a check that whether it's highly similar or not. You won't pick up the content. It's just a check on top of the summary that the actual thing that you are looking for, it is available or not.
Krish Naik: Okay, so another level of check that you can add. Yes, these are all kind of evaluations, in simple terms. Like, you want to be much more confident that, okay, it is available. In those cases, I feel that it is good. Otherwise, a simple summary always gives you a high-level information about the chunk, so works out.
Krish Naik: Well, right now, LLM-based extraction process,
Krish Naik: Not a fan. Now, in this particular implementation, I have not taken the title extractor.
Krish Naik: I don't think I have taken the title extractor. My implementation was only with the summary extractor. Now, please try to implement the title extractor by yourself. I think everybody can do it.
Krish Naik: Yes or no?
Krish Naik: I will just bring the same piece of code here, okay? And, this part, the summary extractor initialization is done.
Krish Naik: So, I will take this piece of code, Let's take… Hmm… This one for a month.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, summary extractor, this has to be changed into title extractor.
Krish Naik: Title extractor…
Krish Naik: Okay, other than that, I don't think there are any, major changes. Note with summary is all right, I think the length of the notes.
Krish Naik: LLM generated summary, let's change that to title.
Krish Naik: Then the rest of the text will be fine.
Krish Naik: And generally, right now, this is the title extractor, let's see how it works.
Krish Naik: Now, somebody was asking, what is the metadata…
Krish Naik: Does not have these fields, like title and summary.
Krish Naik: whatever. So really, there is no if. It means that if you have this.
Krish Naik: from future perspective, see, I always tell you from long-term perspective, if you have small amount of data, and after 5 years, when you have petabytes of data, it becomes very, very hard.
Krish Naik: So, from day one, if you text these steps of making your metadata vibrant, it becomes much easier. At a later stage, you can apply a lot of things. Initially, it won't be much helpful, but after a certain point of time when the organization has grown, okay, it really works a lot.
Krish Naik: Now, E237 is that, what does settings do?
Krish Naik: I think, with respect to settings that I have passed.
Krish Naik: So, right now, the information, if you, really look here, Okay…
Krish Naik: And let me get the metadata also, I have not printed that one.
Krish Naik: Just tweet.
Krish Naik: But God…
Krish Naik: Settings is always, when you are defining your LLM, or your embedding model, or your chunk size, or your overlap, A2317,
Krish Naik: These things in the last notebook I have already discussed, referred to as the global settings.
Krish Naik: Yep.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, let's print out the metadata.
Krish Naik: Okay, so… if…
Krish Naik: Alright, let's take this piece of code.
Krish Naik: Alright, otherwise I can just do this one.
Krish Naik: Let's take this one dot meter top.
Krish Naik: Have I added one title? Just wait.
Krish Naik: Let's look into that, the title part.
Krish Naik: Can you see the extracted title? Attention is only directly the paper information that you are getting.
Krish Naik: Okay?
Krish Naik: So now, see, generally, these type of information, it might be good, like, if you really work with research papers, in those cases, it might be helpful just to get you the title, and keep it in your metadata.
Krish Naik: For a later reference, these type of information, actually. Like, see, this is a document, but really, now this attention is all you need from where all the information might come.
Krish Naik: One, you look into the data, the name of the file can be attention is all you need.pdf.
Krish Naik: These are the common sources from where we can at least… because every time the naming convention with respect to documents, we can't print it.
Krish Naik: Okay, but you can apply this, it gives you an added benefit. If somebody searches about this paper directly in the query, it is really helpful, through filters.
Krish Naik: Alright, Mitesh.
Krish Naik: In the error, the solution is there. Please apply that.
Krish Naik: Yes, I think in one of the projects we do have, I have applied metadata filtering there.
Krish Naik: Metadata filtering is not dynamic, mind.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: Because I don't create dynamic filters, it is fixed.
Krish Naik: Alright, let's look into LLM-based extractions and rule-based extractions. I hope everybody understands the difference. This comes with the cost. Now, in Lama Index, the implementation, like, expensive for sure, but slow, and sequential processing.
Krish Naik: So when, you have the task of sequential processing, what is the first thing? I feel that, how can I make it async?
Krish Naik: Because sequential processing is really, like, a very bad thing in, production. So you have to make this process to an async, and then you have to actually apply in product.
Krish Naik: So we add the title and the summary back to the node as a metadata correct debug. That was the intuition. It means that something we're generating through some custom function.
Krish Naik: Most of the times, when you're creating the metadata, you will be creating your own custom function. Because for the metadata, you have to define a schema that, okay, now, these are the 15, I can say, keys, and for those, how we will extract the values. The values can be through a custom logic, through LLMs.
Krish Naik: And, through from files, because from your original files also, you might get some metadata.
Krish Naik: Now, let's take, let's try to look into node-level relationships. So, when you look into node-level, node-level relationships, simply I mean that chunk-level relationship. And this, previously, I have shown you, so let's show you again this.
Krish Naik: Now here, the information, first of all, total number of nodes that we had, 0123, ID, the relationship that is coming, this is towards source.
Krish Naik: Once everything is connected with one right now, because the main document that we have
Krish Naik: Metadata filtering also helps in speed correct.
Krish Naik: Then comes your node to a similar ID, okay, and the relationship with the source document. Now, this is the document ID. Always remember, don't get confused. And this is the chunk ID.
Krish Naik: Two types are there, so the chunk with the document.
Krish Naik: That you have. So, similarly, now, I want you guys to focus on, remove the sentence notes here. Okay, so what I will do in the code, I will do some changes. Let's try to take that, semantic ones.
Krish Naik: Okay, so… And let's see.
Krish Naik: Here, I will change the sentence to semantic this time.
Krish Naik: I think in no other places I have to do an update, let me just check the source code, I don't feel I need to do it, alright.
Krish Naik: Okay, and how many indexes? Let's… Pick up, I think, just keep it blank, right?
Krish Naik: Okay, so total, all the nodes that I have, so based on that.
Krish Naik: Now, see, has previous node, okay, so node 1, now this information, now see, in semantic chunking, now this information also comes, so I wanted to print out. Now, the first chunk is related to this document.
Krish Naik: Alright, now the second note, if you, really look into the information that you have, this is 2B0, so I know the document has changed this time, the original source document.
Krish Naik: Then comes the relationship, so here, again, I can see this chunk is from the same document. Again, here the document has changed.
Krish Naik: Here, the document is seen.
Krish Naik: Okay, so always, like, for every chunk, based on which document, that particular information, also you can keep. And this information, sometimes people keep it in databases also. Like, for every document, what is the document ID that is getting generated.
Krish Naik: Now, if you really look into this has previous node and the has next node. Now, this relationship, how it is defined from the semantic.
Krish Naik: So the first one, if you really look, see if something is getting started, so for sure it won't have a previous node. Okay, so that's why the node 0, simply, it has no previous relationship, so directly it's telling that, okay, it has the next node available.
Krish Naik: Alright, now for this one. Now, here you can see, for this one, the document is matching, so I can say that
Krish Naik: has mixed…
Krish Naik: node has previous node. When you look into, can I say that this, particular chunk information is after this?
Krish Naik: So now this is, one way to really decode easily, like, in semantic chunking, how the relationship, between the chunks are there. So I know that, okay, first this will come, then this will come into the picture. Similarly, for node 2 and 3,
Krish Naik: Again, initially, if something is starting with, okay, it won't be having a previous note, so that's why the next note that comes, this is completely for a new document. Similarly, for the next one, we know that it has a previous one. If there was chunk 3, then tell me what will happen.
Krish Naik: Sorry, if there is, like, for the first document, okay, because as you can see, these two are related to how many documents?
Krish Naik: A single document, because the document ID is the same, but just think, if you have 3 nodes, then what will be the output?
Krish Naik: Can I say that it has both the nodes, the next node and the previous node? Because right now, my size of the document is small, but you have to understand, it will be having both the information.
Krish Naik: Okay, so that's why that sequencing comes into the picture.
Krish Naik: And really, like, this sequence, I can say somehow it helps in better context phrasing.
Krish Naik: Because, just think about, you got, okay, now this particular node might be better. Now, similarly, can I say that you can look into the next node also?
Krish Naik: You really don't need to look into your main, I can say, because you can apply two conditions, you will say that, okay, let's supply something on source document. Within that source document, if there is… at least, can you look into the next node? If you have these.
Krish Naik: So you are not limited to that, only that information.
Krish Naik: Because your top K results, you cannot be always dependent on the retrieval result.
Krish Naik: at least one level of more information you can bring into the context, I can say, if you have these type of moves.
Krish Naik: You can apply a logic that whether the previous node or the next node exists.
Krish Naik: Okay, if it exists, you can take the information, okay, for your prediction, or basically your query engine, you can pass it there.
Krish Naik: Will Topkeep take both? No. TopK won't be picking up that.
Krish Naik: SB.
Krish Naik: Shubhas is asking, can we ask LLM, like, give me the summary in n number of words using Summary Extractor? Yes, you can… see…
Krish Naik: It is a bit different. Directly, here it is not available.
Krish Naik: Okay, you can make it through probably a custom prompt. Then, directly, you cannot use the function, the summary extractor function for Llama Index.
Krish Naik: Okay, now, this node-level relationship, that's why I showed you in semantic level, they have better meaning. Actually, like, if you directly look into this one, this is, like, simple-level information, but I don't feel it's really so much worth it. The main worthy information, you actually get it through semantic chunking.
Krish Naik: Where you can add more level for better, precision during your retrieval.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, coming, creating custom node relationship. Now, this option is also there. Okay, now you can create this one. So, let's start, like, how the parent chat relationships that have been done in Lama Index. So, we'll be creating parent. So, first of all, let's define some type of text node. So, here, I'm just passing
Krish Naik: This is a custom node that I am creating, and the name of the node is Text Node.
Krish Naik: Okay, so when I'm telling text node, what is the meaning of this?
Krish Naik: I'm creating a chunk by myself.
Krish Naik: How many of you got it?
Krish Naik: Creating chunk by yourself.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: Now, directly, like, in Langchain, you cannot create a chunk.
Krish Naik: See, that's why, when I talk about another framework, you have to understand that, okay?
Krish Naik: how it is different from the other one. And if you really try to compare the power, slowly, slowly, like, after one or two classes, you will feel that, really, like, Llama Index is really powerful.
Krish Naik: Okay, so here… In that information with text and metadata.
Krish Naik: If we can insert metadata, then insert chunks makes sense, no.
Krish Naik: When we will insert my data?
Krish Naik: First.
Krish Naik: You don't… you have to think about both the tasks are independent. That's why. There is no sequence in there. Now, during chunking, when you were saving the embeddings, for those embeddings, we keep the metadata.
Krish Naik: It has to be related for that particular embedding chunk that you have.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, the sequence can be different, like, the way that you are defining, it's not necessarily first.
Krish Naik: You create the metadata, then, like, whichever way, I feel that there are two tasks are there. One is the embedding, one is the metadata creation, however, whichever way. I feel that first, always start work on the embedding, then work on the metadata. That is better.
Krish Naik: Now, here I have defined, now let's take link details note as children. Now, I have to define something that, okay, now for my child notes, what I have done. I have taken sentence notes here.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: And can you see the parent relationship that I have given for which node? So, here I'm passing related node ID, okay? So, let me just take this lineup code here.
Krish Naik: It will be easier to visualize.
Krish Naik: Now, when you look here directly, just see that
Krish Naik: I know I have my child's. Childs I have taken from the sentence printer. So, from that particular note, and here I have taken these many indexes. So, I know that I have 3 different charts. Now, these 3 charts.
Krish Naik: lies under which parent? Now, for that, I am defined. So here, I'm telling that, okay, I've defined a new parent chunk, and in that parent chunk, I'm giving the information.
Krish Naik: related to three things, like research papers on transformers, BERT and RAG. I know that, okay, now this is the actual information that I am having. So, based on that, using this related node info, I'm passing the node ID.
Krish Naik: That I have manually created.
Krish Naik: Okay, and then node.metadata, which level metadata you require, so that's why right here, I'm defining as level 1. Now, this becomes the key.
Krish Naik: Okay, now let's try to look after the execution.
Krish Naik: So, right here, if you directly look into, the information of summary node ID that we have created. So, this node, initially we have created, and right now the node ID for this one is available.
Krish Naik: And for this particular parent node, how many childs I have.
Krish Naik: Three child that were defined, but that was… that information also we were getting.
Krish Naik: Now, tell me, like, child and parent, whenever you work with child and parent, I've already given you an example. Okay, keeping an highly…
Krish Naik: context about all of your charts. It's a good practice to keep it in the period. So here, this is a very high-level summary. You don't have the actual information, but at least very specific keywords that you can look into. I can say some type of intent, majorly, that you have.
Krish Naik: So, we need to know how many nodes are there in each
Krish Naik: a document, no, you don't need to know that, really. Like, when you are creating a parent note, you have to look into at least
Krish Naik: For a single document. Document-wise, if you create parents, I feel that is a better approach.
Krish Naik: Because I can say I have different type of documents.
Krish Naik: Okay, so document label, parent you can create. Sometimes, it means that the parent has to be, like, a differentiator, you have to understand. It means that parent 1 and Parent 2, if you're creating multiple parents, how they are different.
Krish Naik: I don't feel, keeping the same information. There can be conditions. For example, if you are working with only a very similar type of data, where exactly everything is same, only probably the field changes.
Krish Naik: In those cases, I feel that, okay, in the parent information, it can be there. But really, like, on top of… at a later point, if you want to apply some type of embedding.
Krish Naik: or a similar search on top of your parent data, then it becomes a problem. Then, probably, it will show you very similar information. It means that you need to take a decision of how you can derive that differentiator among the parents.
Krish Naik: Is parent and child creation is not a man… nothing is manual, everything can be automated, Srika.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: Alright, now I told you already in what type of label you want to create the parent, that's a decision that needs to be taken from…
Krish Naik: Alright, now let's look into an ingestion pipeline. I feel that this is a very powerful setting, like, in Langchen, it was not there, but if you really look into… I just call a class, within that class, I tell what are the type of transformations I want to do, like center splitter, I pass the embedding model.
Krish Naik: Now, how many of you think that this is, really, like.
Krish Naik: A good approach of upline.
Krish Naik: This is PyTorch way, like, if you have worked with PyTorch, okay, you will feel a very similar settings and environment that you have. I feel that this is a better technique, that's why I really love the ingestion pipelines, whereas in Langshan, do you think there were such things?
Krish Naik: in line, everything through a functional approach that you have to take. So, pretty much clean approach. For developers, I think…
Krish Naik: Okay, now, that's the thing, advanced developers, not newbies.
Krish Naik: For them, I prefer this much more, okay? Now, here I've decided, okay, in this pipeline, I have the information, the sentence text splitter, okay, and then the embedding model.
Krish Naik: Now, in my pipeline, what I need to pass? The documents, or the setup documents, so pipeline.run, documents, sample papers, show progress is equal to 2. Okay, so let's look into how this works.
Krish Naik: So, as simple as that is how quickly this part is done, we would only add…
Krish Naik: And three documents. The splitting mechanism is also sentence splitter. If you take a semantic, you know that you'll be getting the number of nodes as text. Node have embeddings, for sure it will be having, as we have taken the embed model, which is the OpenAI text-based model.
Krish Naik: Now, this approach I really like, which I feel that it is missing.
Krish Naik: I have to create a manual class in Langshan, then I have to create in this way.
Krish Naik: I love this approach as compared to Lansing.
Krish Naik: Hold back.
Krish Naik: Vector stools also you can add.
Krish Naik: not a, deal, Talman. You can do that.
Krish Naik: I've not created an entire rack pipeline. When I'll be doing it, I'll be showing you.
Krish Naik: Now comes in the next step, your vector store index. This part, I have already shown you. Processing our nodes, I feel that. Okay, so in the last example, also, we have taken this, but the data was different. So here, similarity score, again, I'm looking for the top 3 response mode compact.
Krish Naik: Alright, now let's look into your metadata. Based on the question, I think this is related to transformer's architecture, okay?
Krish Naik: the rag output that you have.
Krish Naik: initially… well, right, the major retrib sources we are printing. So here, if you really look into…
Krish Naik: and added a for loop on top of the source nodes. So, response.source notes, you can actually look into what are the top K retrievers that you have.
Krish Naik: Base, like, for the cosine similarity.
Krish Naik: disclosed.
Krish Naik: I'll…
Krish Naik: Really the score, the title, the category, the text preview. Majorly all the information on top of that, the manual metadata.
Krish Naik: Okay, probably that can also come into the picture.
Krish Naik: Now, let's take a simple query.
Krish Naik: Okay, so here also, if I look into…
Krish Naik: Okay, the information that I have is… now, this response is much smaller, so in one shot, I think this is done. It's getting printed here in the console.
Krish Naik: Top information, title is RAG, okay, then authors is related to leaves, and number of citations. This was available directly from the original metadata that we had.
Krish Naik: Can you run the ingestion pipeline? As I got the error, for me it worked, Abhijit. Please do have a check.
Krish Naik: Anybody getting an error when you are running the ingestion pipeline? I don't think you will be getting an error, because simple things are only mentioned. No, no, no, no, alright. Please have a check of each in that case.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, this information. Now, tell me, if you are building a simple rack.
Krish Naik: Okay, because I have not done any third-party external integrations till now.
Krish Naik: Okay, but, the poor logic, because here, the first, that chat or prompt, that particular thing is totally gone. I can bring that into picture, but for now, let's keep it simple.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: So I feel that without that prompt, and right now, yes, there is no change that I am using. So, pretty much, I can say a modular approach, clean approach, as compared to LanChain, the main implementation of track.
Krish Naik: Now, I have taken a simple example. Now, this…
Krish Naik: particular chunk that you have, okay? I want you guys to do something. So, if you remember, you are calculating the top score, the top length. Now, this is a chunk-level analysis, because in the next class, I'll be working with chunk size, like, what are the advanced chunking strategies. So, based on that, please do test it out.
Krish Naik: this part. And I'll be sharing you one more resource, where you will be applying a little bit advanced, and you'll be calculating the faithfulness and probably the relevancy, okay? Or some returable level metrics that also you can take.
Krish Naik: Please, everybody execute this piece of cell. It will take some time, but please execute. Here, I have done nothing, I've just passed the chunk size, and then I'm passing a test query. And based on that, I will be looking into the results.
Krish Naik: Please take this… Okay, and this will take some time.
Krish Naik: And I think I have that.
Krish Naik: because I do have an implementation, I want you guys to do it by yourself, because most of the syntax you guys are familiar. So, like, this is just, like, an assignment that you have to do right now.
Krish Naik: Because I will keep it till chunk size only, nothing… I will go. But this is one. I'm sharing one link.
Krish Naik: Let me first of all show you what is the exact task that I have given you.
Krish Naik: Please do it now.
Krish Naik: New tab. This is from Lava Index, but an older implementation.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, evaluating the ideal chunk size for a rack system using Lama Intex. Okay, now here are a few implementations.
Krish Naik: If you really look into.
Krish Naik: a few things that you will look that might be deprecated, but you need to fix the code. How many of you can do it? First of all, let me know.
Krish Naik: Because this implementation is based on not 14.10.
Krish Naik: It's an older implementation, but I want you guys to go through this, because the content is very much same. Like, if I talk about service context, I think this got deprecated, you need to check what is the replacement in the newer framework.
Krish Naik: Okay? Then, getting the data, so this is UBIT 10K SCC filings data. On top of original data, then setting your evaluators exactly how you want to do your evaluation, take an LLM,
Krish Naik: Then, finally, calculating the faithfulness and relevancy.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: Now, response evaluation for a chunk size. Now, this is the main thing that I want you guys to do, to focus on. Like, if you are actually doing for multiple tests, how you'll be getting the results. So, in your final results, you will be getting a table in that table for every chunk size. What is the information with respect to faithfulness and relevancy?
Krish Naik: Because there is no such thing, like, I feel that this is simple, but you can easily pick it up.
Krish Naik: Okay, please do the implementation, because every time I am speaking, I am doing… but I want you guys at least to start working with the framework.
Krish Naik: Because if you're not starting.
Krish Naik: My plan is, next week, I'll be dipping much more dive into Llama Index, but just focus right now.
Krish Naik: you are not using any third-party services, you are just focused on only one service. So please take your time. This is the task that I am giving. I think by
Krish Naik: 15 to 20 minutes, it should be done. Is it possible in 15 to 20 minutes, the core boilerplate is given? You just need to work on your latest version of Llama.
Krish Naik: Okay, you can do it in your local machine, I have no problem, or do it in Google Collab, whichever way you feel it. Open it in Playground, okay, take a copy, like a new notebook or a copy in some drive or GitHub, then start doing it.
Krish Naik: Because the third notebook, there is basically the integrations with different type of vector databases, but I think in next class, we can start talking about that.
Krish Naik: Do it by yourself, everyone.
Krish Naik: Unable to… why you will be copying? Just click on the link. When I share something in the chat, directly click on the link, you don't need to copy the link.
Krish Naik: Whichever is your default browser, in that browser, this link will open.
Krish Naik: I hope everybody has the access to the link that I have shared. Please let me know.
Krish Naik: Okay, alternate.
Krish Naik: Fine. Will not take much time? Yes, fine, take. Because, at least in live class.
Krish Naik: I can continue and I can tell you, but at least I want from your side, because this is a new framework.
Krish Naik: And probably, I am planning to use Llama Index for majorly, like, time.
Krish Naik: Or at least the remaining track topics.
Krish Naik: use AI, use anything, just be sure the final result I'll be getting something like a table. Okay, the final table, I know there is a…
Krish Naik: I think in the print size, okay, don't…
Krish Naik: Undals is not required, but try to execute it.
Krish Naik: Yes, you can pass your OpenAI. I think the first thing that you have to do is pass the OpenAIT.
Krish Naik: Yeah.
Krish Naik: If you want, you can change, okay, like LavaIndexLot, LLM, if you want, you can change to Gemini, that's not a big deal.
Krish Naik: You can change. I have no issues on that. Just use an LLM.
Krish Naik: So, Lama Index LLM's part, if I go here… Elements.
Krish Naik: Now, the integrations are really long, so using LLMs.
Krish Naik: The usage patterns, okay, now, most of the times, it will be shown for OpenA and Anthropic, as suggested.
Krish Naik: So, ugh.
Krish Naik: Here you can see.
Krish Naik: Like, on top of, like, a custom tokenization can also be applied on top of a model, so that option is also there.
Krish Naik: We support integrations, full list of modules, now check from here. If you guys want to use which one? So, probably, like, the Google one. GGGG, Google Gen AI, okay? Just change the import. You can see this is the package you need to install. For Gemini, guys, I'm sharing the link. Quickly look into the documentation.
Krish Naik: The main purpose is going through the documentation, because Langshan documentation we have gone through multiple times, but with Lama Index, exactly how to browse the documentation.
Krish Naik: Because the things that I might be teaching, it can be deprecated after 2 years, but at least start navigating the docs. It's very important, from dev perspective.
Krish Naik: I think everybody has a Google Gemini key, whoever has not an OpenAPI key, please do these changes, and based on that, you can do the implementation.
Krish Naik: Is this part clear? For Gemini?
Krish Naik: You guys can do it, yes or no.
Krish Naik: I think everybody has Gemini APIs.
Krish Naik: Alright.
Krish Naik: Ulama integrations are also available. So, just go through the documentation, Major League, what are the changes that you need? I know Major League is available here. Open Router is also there. I feel these integrations, if you try to compare with LanChain, LanChain has more integrations, just remember.
Krish Naik: Because it is much more widely adopted, so integrations will be better in Langgin as compared to Lama Index.
Krish Naik: Don't tell me errors right now.
Krish Naik: asyncio.run, then just import that package and fix that issue.
Krish Naik: Next, asyncio, there is a package, you can directly use that to solve whoever is getting asyncio.run issue.
Krish Naik: How big is the PDF?
Krish Naik: PDF, I think, the data that they are using will be big, so…
Krish Naik: No, not this one, I think here… the actual data…
Krish Naik: With 2021, okay, so with data 10K, so at least I know the number of records will be towards higher cent.
Krish Naik: Let me know the document account, or how many characters are there.
Krish Naik: it don't exist my OpenAI limit. Use Gemini, then don't use it. If you feel the data is big, switch to Gemini. I think everybody has Gemini daily free limits.
Krish Naik: Otherwise, you can use Grok also. In this course, I've never talked about Grok, but you can work with Grok.
Krish Naik: So, I think integrations with, Grok is also available here.
Krish Naik: GGGGGG, somewhere, I think.
Krish Naik: G… okay, Grok 4 is there, okay, so Grok is here.
Krish Naik: The X version and the normal one with LPUs.
Krish Naik: Okay, you can use Krog also. From there, you can get open source models. How many of you have used Grok?
Krish Naik: Yes, is there anybody in this class who has not used Croc?
Krish Naik: Can you use Open Router? You can use open router, I have no issue. Whichever, see, I'm showing you the list of integrations. And by this time in this course, I know that you guys are familiar. You have to just change one line of import.
Krish Naik: Yes, only one line of input. So, just click on that link, whichever option that you want. Okay, select the model, okay, and based on that, just check the LLM is working or not in the first step. Then you can use that LLM in here, global settings.
Krish Naik: Because the free options, Grok is one.
Krish Naik: Gemini is one, but, yes, crop models, not very good.
Krish Naik: But again, the Llama models do all the job.
Krish Naik: Oh, please do it.
Krish Naik: Can I change the PDF? You change the PDF if you want, really, like…
Krish Naik: This is too big, fine, change the PDF review field.
Krish Naik: Yeah, really, see, I want you guys to do the experiment, like, what is the ideal chunk size?
Krish Naik: Because I have shown you one simple experiment, but let's take to evaluation level also.
Krish Naik: So that's why this particular notebook… now, this is directly
Krish Naik: Available, so take it. Okay, I will give you 10 to 15 minutes, take your time, do it.
Krish Naik: Use ChatGPT, I have no issues. Use Cloud, I have no issues.
Krish Naik: Naga is telling, I am confused what to do. Just execute the notebook.
Krish Naik: And every cell should be up and working.
Krish Naik: The notebook that I have shared, just be sure it is up and working. Take a smaller set of data, I have no issue.
Krish Naik: Yes, you can do it in any environment, I have no restrictions.
Krish Naik: Think from a dev prospect, you can do it anywhere.
Krish Naik: LLM options, that link also I have shared, so I think everybody can do it.
Krish Naik: In your case, you can reduce the number of questions, because in your PDF, I don't think… okay, so please reduce the number of questions.
Krish Naik: And run from collabal, so I have no issues.
Krish Naik: In collab, the main pain problem that I feel is, like, installing the stuff.
Krish Naik: If something is already installed, you have to do an uninstallation, and then again, a fresh installation. So, yes, you can do it.
Krish Naik: And Gemini users, just use the newer version. I think everybody knows about the new Gemini model release.
Krish Naik: Yes.
Krish Naik: How many of you know new model has been released?
Krish Naik: Please don't work with 2. Try to work with the version 3.
Krish Naik: Yes, Mitesh. Use 3.
Krish Naik: Okay, hey, somebody told I'm getting this error. You have to take that.
Krish Naik: Generally.
Krish Naik: Next asyncure, there is a package. I'm sharing the script, you can check this one, whoever is getting an async error.
Krish Naik: Okay, Subhash has done it, alright.
Krish Naik: So Vash, let's wait for the others.
Krish Naik: Alright, fine, take your time. That's what I've given you for everybody.
Krish Naik: How many of you can do it? That's the main thing. Like, you are trying… is there anybody who is totally stuck? Like, zero idea?
Krish Naik: What we are doing.
Krish Naik: Okay, fine, Aniroth, you use ChatGPT, that is fine, you are using Claud, I have no issues in that.
Krish Naik: But just be sure that how to find out the ideal chunk size based on evaluation.
Krish Naik: Because, with respect to evaluators, you already know.
Krish Naik: But, setting up the custom evaluation and these things, That are important.
Krish Naik: Generally, like, this relationship, nobody talks about.
Krish Naik: How is your response evaluation? Like, is there a relationship between your chum size?
Krish Naik: Iran Rathot, if you're getting the error, please solve it. I'm not going to solve, that's why I've given you the task, you need to do it.
Krish Naik: I did for 4 questions, small PDF. Okay, alright.
Krish Naik: So, Vash, you have done, done for how many questions?
Krish Naik: And how many documents, like… Let me know that number also.
Krish Naik: done for one question. Please increase the number of questions of us. That's why you are getting a very high faithfulness and a high answer relevancy. Please increase the number of questions.
Krish Naik: MS, sorry for 5 you have done. Alright, fine. At least take something, yes, more than one, that is the idea.
Krish Naik: Yes, Sonali, I know.
Krish Naik: That's why I've given you the task, no?
Krish Naik: Otherwise, direct run, run, run, that was not the idea.
Krish Naik: You need to fix.
Krish Naik: There will be minor changes. I won't say there will be a lot of big changes.
Krish Naik: Some minor changes that you need to do it in runtime. Now.
Krish Naik: Please provide me the updates in the chat.
Krish Naik: Okay, so Mithesh is asking, species used for generating the question, I suppose.
Krish Naik: GPT-4O, GPT-4 is fine. It's not so much expensive as compared to 4.0 MS.
Krish Naik: You can, pick something like GPT-5C. For evaluation, you need a better model.
Krish Naik: Just remember that. So, for now, if you want, use the same model.
Krish Naik: Now, how many of you think spaCy has been used here for generating the questions?
Krish Naik: Please let me know in the chat.
Krish Naik: Are we using spacing for question generation?
Krish Naik: Yes, we are even specie.
Krish Naik: Look into the logs, because even I don't have logs right now.
Krish Naik: Okay, from the logs, you can do that.
Krish Naik: Okay, Janika, you need to solve that error. Whatever error you are getting.
Krish Naik: Right now, in this course, if you are getting a module not found error, please don't ask me.
Krish Naik: You need to solve this by yourself.
Krish Naik: When you look into module not found error, it simply means the package is missing. You need to take care of the installation of the package.
Krish Naik: No, I'm not going to, right now, share a screen.
Krish Naik: Many models are economical, yes.
Krish Naik: Generally, for response, you can do for evaluation, just be sure you use a better model.
Krish Naik: at least see, why I want to show this particular example. First, it has a very good utility. What is the choosing the perfect chunk size?
Krish Naik: You create a program, or a function, or a package, and this package you can directly apply on top of a set of documents.
Krish Naik: Can we create a package?
Krish Naik: And based on that, whatever the results that I'm getting, directly, I can decide.
Krish Naik: Yes or no?
Krish Naik: And always, you have to do it on the subset of a data, not on your… on top of your entire dataset. Nobody does it. Take a subset, on top of that, you have to apply.
Krish Naik: I think it is going to be 12. Trishi Chunk 1, average response time 1, okay?
Krish Naik: That is for only one chunk that you have, Rishi. For the other chunks, if you are increasing the chunk, then what happens?
Krish Naik: Okay, the rest is processing, fine, I believe it.
Krish Naik: you really, need to look into, I think, 3 parameters are there. The average response time, the average faithfulness, and the average relevancy.
Krish Naik: So, when the chunk size is increasing, do you feel that the faithfulness is increasing?
Krish Naik: All the relevancy is increasing.
Krish Naik: If you are increasing that, if
Krish Naik: based on those parameters, you can actually pick up that, okay, it's fine, then I can actually use this particular chunk size.
Krish Naik: So, based on those two parameters, average response is fine, like, I know there will be a certain difference among the
Krish Naik: I can say the responses, but it will be in milliseconds.
Krish Naik: really, like, probably, I think, from 155 to 157, somewhere 160, but it will be close around.
Krish Naik: But the major factor, which is the faithfulness and the relevance in that part I want you guys to focus on.
Krish Naik: Okay, chun size 128. Let's wait for the entire processing. I know the processing will take time. Wait.
Krish Naik: I think in the next class we can do it, not a big one.
Krish Naik: Let's see at least how many of you can do it.
Krish Naik: Because in the third notebook, we have only some external integrations with vector databases.
Krish Naik: That's the only part which is remaining. I have shared, you can always go through the code. Let's say today we'll be discussing, otherwise next week, Saturday.
Krish Naik: Everybody is telling import error, cannot import names simple directory reader from Lama Index.
Krish Naik: If you're getting this error, now really you have to look into…
Krish Naik: Now, Satish is asking why I'm getting this error.
Krish Naik: Yes.
Krish Naik: Mmm…
Krish Naik: Really, you need to look into what is the issue, check with the versions of Llama Index which is available. If there is a version mismatch, you will be getting an error. By this time, see, guys, I will take that you guys know how to resolve at least package dependency issues.
Krish Naik: Please do have a check with the versions, and you have to meet your code compatible. At least pick up something from the recent version. You have two options. One, use the older version. If you know, if you don't know the older version, you have to make the code compatible to the newer version.
Krish Naik: In whichever way you want to go at it.
Krish Naik: It's fine, you were using 0. Now you have to check from that.
Krish Naik: I'm just telling it is moved under .core.evaluation, the directory. Read that part, okay? Alright.
Krish Naik: So, somebody has shared me a set of imports, I am just sharing it.
Krish Naik: Okay, E2317, thanks for sharing this one. For others, I'm sharing it in the chat. You can take a referral for the evaluation part exactly from where it is getting imported.
Krish Naik: Yes, fine, I have already shared with others also.
Krish Naik: Okay, yes.core, that llamaindex.core, correct, Rishi.
Krish Naik: Space installation going for you.
Krish Naik: Okay, space installation, what is space installation? I could not get it.
Krish Naik: I might have to define, then. I won't be discussing anything new, okay, so you guys can…
Krish Naik: Okay, spacey, already spaCy, basic, fine.
Krish Naik: Spacey is really, like, one of the best libraries, I can say. Like, from… back from 2018, I have been working with
Krish Naik: Explosion AI, because PC comes from the Explosion AI team.
Krish Naik: Okay, and really, the development that they have shown is really good.
Krish Naik: They are lesser into research, much more towards applied stuff.
Krish Naik: For production-grade pipelines, even I suggest spaCy. For tasks like NER, name entity recognition, works very, very good. Then, coming to posh tag, parts of speech, spaCy. By default, the settings.
Krish Naik: Okay, Mantach cannot import, alright.
Krish Naik: Yes, I want you guys to focus on Lama Index, there is just one purpose.
Krish Naik: Because next classes, I'm going to teach you those topics on Lama Intex, that's why.
Krish Naik: Because Langchen, you will be familiar, I know. Like, Langchen, I feel that everywhere, Langchen, Langchen, Langchen is there. Llama Index is somewhere less.
Krish Naik: But if you're a developer with more than 5 to 6 years of experience, I will say that you will enjoy Lama Intex better than Landshake. It's just the developer experience is better.
Krish Naik: I feel. Langchain has more integration, more support, the issues get solved much better, I can say, but here also, the same thing, the speed can be slow with respect to the contributions as compared to Langchain, but really, like,
Krish Naik: clean code. In Langchain, there's really not so much pain that I feel.
Krish Naik: Any year, like, more than 5 to 6.
Krish Naik: Developer's choice, I will say. And you know that, people don't love developers, that's why that…
Krish Naik: If some package is left, really, the number of stars you will see always towards the lower side.
Krish Naik: Because then next, during chunking, I'll be talking about a live DD. Okay, so chunky.
Krish Naik: Now, this library is only used for, chunking, the major, chunking library right now, the famous one in the market.
Krish Naik: We'll be looking into the open source version of this one.
Krish Naik: Okay, so I think somewhere there will be docs.
Krish Naik: chunky documentation, okay? So, here. In the next class, we'll be talking about chunky with respect to chunking more. Here you have major concepts, okay, all these things. The documentation is really good for chunky.
Krish Naik: And even for Chonky, the main developer.
Krish Naik: With, the main developer, also, I'm connected in Reddit.
Krish Naik: I hope this applies. Is this Atlas browser? No, no, this is not Atlas, this is DAIA. D-I-A.
Krish Naik: Yes, please let me know, guys, for how many of you it has done, and for all the chunk sizes, you are getting the response.
Krish Naik: Rishi, I think you are done till 1024. Fine, let's wait for 2048. Okay, and then I can ask you. People you have done, I can ask you to share your screen and to show your result.
Krish Naik: Just check, it will be in the import section of your shit. Somewhere. Within your logs, you will see that space, it will come.
Krish Naik: I have not executed, but others who have done, they can show it.
Krish Naik: Alright, I think Rohit has executed, he is showing shank 2048. There is a drop in, okay.
Krish Naik: The faithfulness score is 0.60, okay, and…
Krish Naik: The relevance is also close to 6.60. When the numbers match, I know, like, the document is smaller and lesser number of questions.
Krish Naik: For bigger questions, it will be bigger.
Krish Naik: I'm alright.
Krish Naik: For Richey, okay, for chunk size, 512, I can see 0.97, and the answer relevancy is also 0.85.
Krish Naik: Churn size 1024, average faithfulness is coming close to 0.95.
Krish Naik: They have a very similar results. Good.
Krish Naik: Subhash, for 20 documents with 10 questions, the result is as below, chunk 128, okay, 0.80, 0.57, the relevancy is towards the lower side. You increase the chunk size, the faithfulness has dropped by, okay.02, the relevancy has increased.
Krish Naik: Okay, in the third case, the faithfulness is same, but
Krish Naik: Average relevancy, again, that has decreased.
Krish Naik: Okay, so a perfect one, 0.8 with 0.57. So I can set at chunk size 1024 sulash.
Krish Naik: it is working good for him, okay? Like, based on your results, I can say chunk 1024.
Krish Naik: Alright, now coming to Anirud. Anirud, you have very similar values. How many questions, Anirud, you have passed?
Krish Naik: Because 0.75111. Because, see, this value will change based on more questions.
Krish Naik: Actually, when you'll be working, remember, you have to pass more and more questions. For the sake of this class, it's fine you are using less, but actually, when you take this and you try to do the implementation, okay? So, please use more and more questions, because I know the set of documents will be higher.
Krish Naik: Koshan to 5 all right, Rohit. Rajat?
Krish Naik: In your case, answer relevancy, okay. For, chunk 128, the relevancy is less.
Krish Naik: So, for you, you are getting results, like, 1-1, and the response time when I look into, like, chunk size 512 and 1024, both are working. So, in this case, Rajat, in your case, I can say 512 is working good.
Krish Naik: Okay, Rishi, fine. Too many reentries, fine.
Krish Naik: Okay, chunk size 2048, alright.
Krish Naik: RT equal colony quotients is equal to 40. RT…
Krish Naik: Are you showing me your results? I don't think you have passed. Please share it in the chat.
Krish Naik: Okay, you are sharing fine for 2 chunk sizes, 128, 256. 0.9, 0.9, okay, both the values are pretty much the same.
Krish Naik: Execution time will be very high, for sure, because, see, the evaluation process takes time.
Krish Naik: Even during Raga's section, if you remember, I just left the cell execution for more than 10 minutes. It will take time.
Krish Naik: Yes, this notebook.
Krish Naik: Evaluation comes with a price, always remember that.
Krish Naik: Yes, I think we are done, majorly today.
Krish Naik: Now, anybody can share with a notebook, like, make the notebook, with a public link.
Krish Naik: Okay, a view… at least give me the view access, so that at least I can share with others. Anybody can do that.
Krish Naik: Who has, those, print statements?
Krish Naik: Okay, for the different, test site in your notebook. Do a Ctrl-S, click on share, and share me the notebook link with View Access. Please.
Krish Naik: Anyone can do that.
Krish Naik: Rishi, MS, please do.
Krish Naik: Nabil, you are getting a rate limiter.
Krish Naik: 10 documents, 20 questions. All right, Murta… Nugish, response time, okay.
Krish Naik: The response time, now,
Krish Naik: The common trend is, like, if you increase the chunk size, the response time will always increase.
Krish Naik: Okay, so really, don't focus on response time. If you feel that there is such a case where your faithfulness and your relevancy
Krish Naik: are saying. Okay, then you can only focus on those… the other parameter, which is the response time. Otherwise, the major focus should be faithfulness and relevancy, how they are changing, the up and downs.
Krish Naik: Okay, Abhijit, alright, chunk size, 512, but what about the other chunks? I was looking for that.
Krish Naik: 1024 and 2048 also. Okay, Rajat has shared, I think. Let me open Rajat Sync.
Krish Naik: Okay, all over the right…
Krish Naik: No, Rajat, I think here, nothing, there is no output only.
Krish Naik: I don't think this is the one. Please share the correct notebook.
Krish Naik: Okay, you have down… I downloaded, but let me upload, okay, fine.
Krish Naik: Rishi, anyone, like, you can share. It's just for the reference for others.
Krish Naik: Who might get stuck for them.
Krish Naik: Because the code is deprecated, I know many of you can't upgrade it to the new version.
Krish Naik: Just share me. If somebody's doing it in local or in collab, just share me a link, okay? Try this, uploaded mine, alright.
Krish Naik: Hmm…
Krish Naik: Alright, so here, Lama Index part, you loaded up your own document, this is fine.
Krish Naik: 10K, OpenAI completions, alright. Setting up your evaluators. This piece of code, you have commented, alright.
Krish Naik: For others, I think they can easily take up this one, query evaluations.
Krish Naik: Now, here, there is a simple error, but
Krish Naik: This is a type error, missing one argument with eval questions.
Krish Naik: Have you corrected?
Krish Naik: The error is coming from this one.
Krish Naik: Open metadata, let me see, like, I have not worked with open metadata, let me see…
Krish Naik: This is not a framework, I feel. Let me see for, open metadata.
Krish Naik: PYPI… because it should have an open source version.
Krish Naik: To build the open material, I have added a folder to a file system.
Krish Naik: CPI.
Krish Naik: Okay, this is 11 years ago, really an old one.
Krish Naik: This is a recent version that they have.
Krish Naik: Let me go to the source page once.
Krish Naik: Try our sandbox, install and run.
Krish Naik: They're providing sandbox-based environments. Look like part of the product.
Krish Naik: Not committed, open consumer.
Krish Naik: They… they don't have a PYPI version only. It means that, for our purpose, I don't think this will be so much helpful. For enterprise purpose, it can be.
Krish Naik: Alright, anybody else share the link with me? Please let me know in the chat.
Krish Naik: Raja, again, you have shared a link, Anirud has shared, let me open his link.
Krish Naik: Why it's asking for this online changes to Twitter.
Krish Naik: crop people in.
Krish Naik: Please give me, access, whoever is doing this.
Krish Naik: People who are sharing with me, at least be sure you are giving me the access.
Krish Naik: Abhijinth…
Krish Naik: Again, many people are sharing, but they are not giving the access.
Krish Naik: Please provide access. Mine you can check, okay?
Krish Naik: Alright, now this looks perfect to me. I think Rajesh shared.
Krish Naik: Alright, now this notebook link I'll be sharing with everyone, because it looks, here, the perfect result. Now, when you look into
Krish Naik: You have to do the analyze from this, okay? And the main focus should be towards faithfulness and relevancy. So in this case, if I'm going with lower chunk size.
Krish Naik: for sure, like, I can say this is a good option, but in both the places. But in the next chunk, I can see that there has been an increase in the
Krish Naik: Relevancy, similarly, like, 512, this is a good spot.
Krish Naik: Okay, and similarly for this one. No, so I told you, pick anything above 512, that's the…
Krish Naik: Same thing that come…
Krish Naik: Here, 1-1 in both the cases, and chunk size 2048, somehow the faithfulness will drop now.
Krish Naik: Now, the response time was much higher. A general trend, I can say, that once you start increasing the chunk size, the response time should be higher.
Krish Naik: But in this case, For a small chunk size, the response was high, 203.
Krish Naik: you doubled it, then it decreased, then it decreased, really. Like, this was somehow strange. Most of the times, in other experiments we have seen, like, as the chunk size increases, the response time also increases. Because bigger the chunk, bigger the time to process for the LL.
Krish Naik: Rishi, alright, you have shared. Can you check the code? No keys exposed.
Krish Naik: Okay, here I hope no key is here.
Krish Naik: Fine, alright.
Krish Naik: Now… Rajata, Shayar, Riti, others. Alright then, I think,
Krish Naik: This notebook I can directly access, I can share this link with others also. People who have not attempted, at least please go through this part.
Krish Naik: Okay, you are asking, I don't think you have passed anywhere that, OpenAIG definition.
Krish Naik: No, I don't think you have passed. Otherwise, just delete your OpenAI API key, if you are in doubt.
Krish Naik: I don't feel you have passed it here.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, just remember now, I just kept this part just you guys to focus on one thing.
Krish Naik: What is the ideal size? And now, this is one of the finest way to do it.
Krish Naik: There is no other way or no rule which has been properly defined.
Krish Naik: Always check based on the response evaluation. Take a subset of the data.
Krish Naik: And do the testing. Use a good LLM, okay? Like, probably pick up something from the reasoning family, okay? Use those.
Krish Naik: And once you have decided, because you know that blindly I can use 1024, I know 512 to 1024 really works. Something in between also I can pick up, like 736, 800, these are the numbers that I actually work in production. It's not necessary, it has to be always 2 to the power n.
Krish Naik: Okay, so that logic is not important. 2 to the power n logic comes whenever we are working with GPUs much more. If we are not working with GPUs, really, that doesn't matter to us.
Krish Naik: Alright, Rishi, okay. How much you guys have spent? Okay, so, MS toll close to $1. Rishi, again, close to $1, alright.
Krish Naik: Gemini guys? Anybody? Gemini? With,
Krish Naik: No, Nabil 0.86, okay, totally depends upon… depends upon the number of questions that you have selected.
Krish Naik: Fine, so I've already provided you the solution, people who have not attempted, please go through the solution at least.
Krish Naik: I think this is possible by yourself, and in this notebook, there is no such thing that you guys don't know. Everything has been discussed with you.
Krish Naik: There was nothing new.
Krish Naik: one requirement was there, you just need to update the package, and based on that, the syntax part that you need to update. And I think most of you have done, it's good.
Krish Naik: Because in the next class, then, third-party integrations with Vector 2, that we will start.
Krish Naik: All right, now let's come to the part. Now, I think I can start taking questions. People who are doing it, you can do. Now, let me…
Krish Naik: Focus on the questions… Next class, Notebook 3, we'll be discussing in the next class.
Krish Naik: Okay, so let's start with Mitesh, Tuosh…
Krish Naik: And I think Naga, you people are there, Rahul is there.
Krish Naik: Here's one way when you guys can go ahead.
Mitesh Shah: Yeah, so, Matesha, a very basic thing that… async thing that we were getting, right?
Krish Naik: Tilted.
Mitesh Shah: Yeah, that's because, typically, when, yeah, when we are overloading them with a lot of data, and it would be in the internal architecture when a sync will be called.
Krish Naik: Yes, generally, see, in Jupyter Notebooks, the problem comes. If you're working in your scripts, like .py files, there you won't be having the issue. Like, you will be using the package nest async queue, and directly you can apply all of your asynchronous calls.
Mitesh Shah: So now, if I want to update this, right, I tried importing the statement and everything, then it failed because
Mitesh Shah: The next print statement fails. I'm talking about the second notebook, where we were trying to print the nodes with summary and the text and the title extractor that we were trying to do.
Krish Naik: It's lean.
Krish Naik: It's, like, it's failing, it means you were telling that nest async, your package is not working.
Mitesh Shah: Okay, now let me re-implement it, then.
Krish Naik: See, just have a check. I feel that there will be a minor issue.
Mitesh Shah: Hmm.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Krish Naik: Because majorly for everybody, it has worked, so just have a check on that.
Mitesh Shah: We'll check it. Thank you.
Krish Naik: Next.
Rahul Parihar: Hey, Paul, so this question is, of yesterday. I'm doing a… CI-CD deployment, and my…
Rahul Parihar: Deployer for app runner is fail… is saying it's green, but the app is not, in the AWS console, it's, saying it's been dying, and it's the.
Krish Naik: So, check the application logs. From the application log, they will be getting the information related to app.
Rahul Parihar: Yeah, I checked the application logs,
Rahul Parihar: It's saying the port is not, AT80 port is not getting configured, and it's working locally.
Rahul Parihar: But it's not…
Krish Naik: Okay, fine, then change the port, update it to 8000.
Rahul Parihar: Okay.
Rahul Parihar: Let me try that.
Krish Naik: Next.
Krish Naik: Ahmed, Rajat… Okay, Armani, a few people I have unmuted, so one by one.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Okay, I'm here.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: So, actually, I couldn't be able to attend the class, but where are the GitHub actions? Is it separate file, or is it in a Docker file?
Krish Naik: It is in data workflows, no?
Krish Naik: That folder is there. Please do have a check.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Okay, finally…
Krish Naik: there is a .gitub folder. Inside that, there will be a workflow folder. Within that workflow, you have your CI and deploy.ympto files.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Okay, got it. So, now, that… I thank you. Okay, then the next question is, you explained different, chunking methodologies, let's say sentence and, other ones. So, what are the… I mean, can you give me practical applications where we can use different…
Krish Naik: It depends upon your data.
Krish Naik: There is… you have to analyze your data. If you feel that in your data, there are a lot of, like, those things, single lines, paragraphs, headers, and other stuff. In those cases, I feel that recursive Character Splitter really works good. You won't have any issue.
Krish Naik: But if you feel that your text is really a long, big paragraph of 20 to 30 pages, in those cases, it might fail.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Okay.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: And, so, okay, so based on… but in our case, right, let us say we are analyzing a set of documents, okay?
Armani, Bhagwan Das: we don't know what the format it would be, then how do we decide in that case? I mean, I'm trying to relate whatever you explained to the practical…
Krish Naik: This is never possible, like, you have to take at least, for example, people who are building rack-based products. Okay. Now, based on documents, they will be using the parser.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: God.
Krish Naik: That's the job of your parser, to make it. So, the intermediate format the whole industry uses is that, okay, so from one document format, they will bring to the universal format the most friendly format, which is mantong.
Krish Naik: So, from Markdown, that will go.
Krish Naik: to, your main chunks. So on top of the markdown file, you apply chunks.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Okay, and if it is a tabular kind of data, or…
Krish Naik: That is different.
Krish Naik: In those cases, like, row-wise, you will be doing it.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: That is one of the, like, for every recording, might do it.
Krish Naik: Then again, it depends, like, what is the size of the data.
Krish Naik: SQL, till now, I have not told you about. I think. In your next project, SQL will also, I will include.
Krish Naik: It's already included.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Okay, thanks. So, Muti, whenever you explain next time, right, you give me some… I mean, maybe it helps others as well. Give me how we… where we can use this practically, like, that's how… because I'm always trying to…
Armani, Bhagwan Das: fit and understand, but I was breaking them, and I was trying to… critic.
Krish Naik: Okay, you have to take multiple, data documents, okay, and then you have to analyze on top of that. Just create a for loop, within that for loop, pass the initializer, and just try to analyze the result for different types of… let us know how exactly it looks like.
Krish Naik: That is the best way. You have to find always, you have to do, like, a simple, let's do not refer to as hyperparameter, but you can pass those as parameters, and based on that, you can always look
Krish Naik: In a for loop, in the first loop, pass your set of documents, probably 3 documents. On top of those 3 documents apply 4 to 5 different types of spitters. You will get that.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Okay.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Okay, so it is, like, more of a IML where we don't have a state answer, we have to do trial and error.
Krish Naik: Yes, directly, like, somebody asked me in the chat what is the best… nothing called as best. It depends totally upon unit.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Okay.
Krish Naik: If you have some type of mathematical formulas, then it will change.
Krish Naik: So that's why, like, it totally depends upon the content. If you have images, then again, it will change. So, that's why. You have to analyze the data.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Gotcha.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Okay.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Thanks. Thank you.
Krish Naik: Alright, next.
Krish Naik: to wherever else they can go.
Amit Singh: Oh.
Krish Naik: jerk, sampat, your quadrant tissue. Yes, yes, please go ahead.
Amit Singh: I just… I'm facing… Hi, Paul, sir. I'm facing an issue with the Docker image build.
Amit Singh: I moved the…
Krish Naik: Show me, show me, like, these issues, CICD issues, without seeing is very hard. I'm adding you to panelists. Please, share.
Amit Singh: Yeah, sure.
Krish Naik: Next.
Rajat Khanna: Rajit, they said.
Krish Naik: Yaraja.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, so, my first question is regarding a normal query that I am getting. For example, like, we are creating chunks and store in VectorDB, right?
Rajat Khanna: We can do it, like, whilst not storing in the vector DB. Can we store the data in a normal DB and just normally do an API, like, in normal SQL and NoSQL, we use, create APIs on top of that? So those things can be done?
Krish Naik: You can do that, but for that, you have to pick up such DBs.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish Naik: Okay, like, for example, if you are working with Oracle 26 AI, you can't do that.
Krish Naik: The thing that you were telling. It means that the DB should support SQL-based operations as well as vector DB operations.
Rajat Khanna: There are few products in the market who support that.
Rajat Khanna: No, no, so the question is regarding… I have a… you can say I have a normal PDF, okay, and I want to store those PDFs as in, while converting into relational… store it in relational data.
Krish Naik: Alright, you were telling me you will be saving the chunks in a RDS, as simple as that.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah.
Krish Naik: Okay, now you have to think that when you're saving it to RDS, if you want to do a matching algorithm, a similarity score algorithm, how you will do it?
Krish Naik: Vectors are going to work.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, yeah.
Krish Naik: Okay, now you have to think about, alright, then you can move towards your, like, sparse-based techniques, like VM25 algorithm. Those things can work.
Krish Naik: But vector search won't work. That's why I'm telling you, select a DB which is capable of doing SQL-based operations, as well as vector DB operations, graph operations. Few DBs are there in the market, which helps you to do that.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, and one issue I face, generally while running, the, books, the Jupyter notebooks that you provide, if a particular memory store value increases, the kernel crashes for me.
Rajat Khanna: So, for example, like, I'm doing embedding, or I'm doing, storing, not storing in a separate DB file, only we are creating those values in the memory. So, if I run the next cell, the kernel crashes. So, it is because of I'm using a normal M1 error.
Rajat Khanna: Or is that me some other issue?
Krish Naik: Generally, most of the times, the kernel crash happens when, like, one instance of a certain variable is initialized, and then again, you try to reinitialize. Then that deadlock happens, and because of that, the kernel fails, most of the time.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, for me means what debugging I have done, and I have asked the chat GPT, so it is saying, like, there is a certain value, of MBs that can hold in Jupyter Notebook, like these cells, and if we increase those, values, then the kernel crashes.
Krish Naik: Increase those values, really? I… increase those values?
Rajat Khanna: That means we can say, like, 20KB, 30KB, memory.
Krish Naik: No, no, no, no, no, no. I have worked with 100MB of Jupyter notebooks, so I don't think that is the problem. Notebooks can be big, because, like,
Krish Naik: There was one scenario, like, very old, I'm telling you, like, in production, we have used Jupyter Notebooks back in 2018. Like, the entire team was not good with modular coding and this stuff. Okay, so, like, it doesn't happen that way.
Krish Naik: I won't say if the memory or the size of the Jupiter notebook increases, I don't feel that should be the issue. It has to be some type of locking mechanism or a SIMA4 block that happens. Like, in OS level, I'm talking about.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, okay. And, just normal, like, when you add, notes in the, your, iPad, so, in Notion, those are not attached, so can you please attach two days? Means previous few classes.
Krish Naik: Previous classes, just wait, I think I have added…
Krish Naik: But when you do that, just wait, let me just start with this one.
Krish Naik: Alright, so just with motion… In the last two classes, it was all about project, I think.
Krish Naik: So, the project classes, there was no major… No, not for the project, previous ones, like…
Rajat Khanna: 3 weeks back.
Krish Naik: was majorly practical just, but I will change, check my iPad, what was the recent note in your batch.
Krish Naik: I think, one was with respect to your…
Krish Naik: Past API, data passes… there was no such main information what was there, so I've not uploaded it. In data passes, yes, there was one.
Krish Naik: But, when I look into… yes, it's not there.
Krish Naik: Fine, I will add that part.
Krish Naik: It's there, I'll just take a copy, and I'll update.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, okay, that's it. Just, just reply on that mail that when I.
Krish Naik: Yes, yes, yes, this week I will try to connect with you, okay?
Rajat Khanna: Okay, thank you.
Krish Naik: Okay, now, Amit, your Docker issues, show me, like, where it's getting failed.
Amit Singh: I was initially getting an error, and I commented the code of that production stage.
Krish Naik: I'll add more to those later on.
Amit Singh: then it… then I went ahead and again tried it. It's, like, unable to… I'm getting a… it's unable to create a copy.
Krish Naik: No, it's not unable to… this is a command. Copy command, it means from…
Krish Naik: to, the destination, to the Docker destination, and there you are copying from your local…
Krish Naik: to the, to the Docker image.
Krish Naik: And now, why this is coming? Because…
Krish Naik: You can't perform a copy operation.
Krish Naik: By talking.
Amit Singh: Looker file is correctly placed, right? I mean, it's in the root, right? I moved it from.
Krish Naik: There is another solution for you, okay? You have to go inside the Docker image and manually create the file.
Krish Naik: If you are facing this, like.
Krish Naik: But one by one, I think close to 4 or 5 files that you need to create.
Krish Naik: Okay. That is the other solution that I know, that through docker exec hyphen IT, you can do that.
Krish Naik: Okay, I'm just sharing you one command.
Krish Naik: Fair enough.
Krish Naik: You have to log in into the image, and after login into the image, you really need to check.
Amit Singh: Login into the image, okay? So it's not clear…
Krish Naik: You have to sign in into or log in into the image that we call it.
Krish Naik: Okay, I'm just sharing you…
Amit Singh: I can do it. If you just tell me the steps, I'll definitely look at it at…
Krish Naik: Try this one I'm sharing, one in the chat.
Krish Naik: Okay, till now, you don't have the image plated only, then you can't log into the image.
Amit Singh: Yes, that is what…
Krish Naik: Right now.
Krish Naik: You don't have the image only release, so in that purpose.
Krish Naik: See, changing the operating system, I know instantly it will start working.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Amit Singh: Well, that is my personal experience, that's why I'm telling you.
Krish Naik: Because, see, just quickly, just to show you, okay, do you have an office email ID?
Krish Naik: Using which you can say, I need a work email. Anything, like, it's not office, any work type email, not at the right Gmail.
Amit Singh: Yeah, I have, yes, I have.
Krish Naik: Okay, alright, you can log into that particular account and sign up in Lightning AI quickly. I will just do the testing right now.
Amit Singh: Okay. We will clone the repo, and directly we will execute the docker test.
Krish Naik: Quickly open your browser and switch to Lightning.
Krish Naik: But do you want me to show? I can do it in a faster way.
Amit Singh: Okay, yes, please.
Krish Naik: Oh, like…
Krish Naik: Advanced, okay, screen 3, I think this is my desktop 3, 1, 2, 3. I have to just check for credit in which account I do have the credits.
Amit Singh: So I've got… got to go to Lightning AI, right?
Krish Naik: Yes, I'm just showing… just see my screen.
Krish Naik: This is already logged?
Krish Naik: Where is Studio, studio, studio, build…
Krish Naik: This interface has changed, it looks like. I'm opening after a long time.
Krish Naik: But,
Krish Naik: Just wait, I will change my browser once.
Krish Naik: Alright, this is the actual one I was looking for. Fine. Now, do I have credits? Yes, I do have credits, a new studio. AI development… I don't need a GPU, so probably let me go ahead with the CPU, fine.
Krish Naik: I'm going to be using… I need AWS, AWS. Do I have an AWS that's not available for me?
Krish Naik: Now I need the GitHub repo.
Krish Naik: Okay, so GitHub repo, I think, this is a Llama Index repo.
Krish Naik: Alright, the project class repo you are working with?
Krish Naik: Not to show es…
Krish Naik: Because of working with us.
Krish Naik: Tanned alone.
Krish Naik: I will… Pick up, I think, get here… we'll copy it, fine.
Amit Singh: Can't we resolve it in local, like, I mean, from the Windows or Windows itself?
Krish Naik: I don't know, because if you can't create, this is probably some type of permission issue that comes.
Krish Naik: Because I know the Docker should work. I have tested it more than 3 times.
Krish Naik: So, if you want me to test in some other place, that is the, like, only solution.
Krish Naik: You can test it at any OS. If it works here, it means that there is some OS level issue that you need to resolve.
Amit Singh: Okay.
Krish Naik: The OS is loaded, I think, yes.
Krish Naik: What is the shortcut including cloning in VS Code?
Krish Naik: Anybody be a school?
Krish Naik: It's Ctrl-Shift-P, okay, alright. Control-Shift-P, Command-Shift-P, I think.
Krish Naik: Yes, gloom.
Krish Naik: Okay, domino.
Krish Naik: Alright, now I'm adjusting these… Don't relevant.
Krish Naik: D.
Amit Singh: Yeah, it's executing.
Krish Naik: Because Docker files are generic, it can work in any environment, if you have that repo with it.
Krish Naik: Because I feel it should work, there won't be any problem, that's why.
Krish Naik: If your Docker don't have certain level of access, I don't know. In Windows, really, like, Docker development and other things in Windows, I'm… that's why not a very fan of this one.
Krish Naik: The entire DevOps runs in Linux-based servers.
Amit Singh: Got it, okay.
Krish Naik: Okay, because I feel that it is working, but let's see the production step.
Krish Naik: Only the last two steps, yes, exporting to image layers means that the build is done.
Krish Naik: Well, early inches.
Krish Naik: Here are the images.
Amit Singh: So your third.
Krish Naik: You have to check, because, like, if something is not getting, probably some permission-level issues that you have.
Krish Naik: Or sometimes the script needs to be changed, but I don't feel the script needs to be changed.
Krish Naik: Because, like, it should work in any environment, at least, like, I have done the testing, and other Windows users have not told, you were the first one. I feel some type of…
Krish Naik: OS level permission issued at you.
Amit Singh: So, Lightning AI, we just tested it, right? But I have to… got to do it on local only, right? And then, test it, locally, and then export, export the whole image to Amazon ECR, right?
Krish Naik: Hmm.
Krish Naik: Correct.
Krish Naik: From here, also, you'll do it. From Lightning AI, you can do everything in one shot.
Krish Naik: If you want to test it, at least for your own practical learning, it's a great place.
Krish Naik: Yeah, everything comes installed. I think AWS also comes installed, CLI and other things.
Amit Singh: So… I mean, I'll have to start all over again on Lightning Air, that is what you are suggesting?
Krish Naik: You… see, it's just the environment, you can use any… there are so many environments, like AWS, SageMaker, and others also provide the same thing, but quick prototyping and testing, I prefer Lightning.
Krish Naik: If you feel that somehow in your system you can't do it, then I'm asking you, you can switch it. You can… if you have a Google, like, collab is also fine, you can do it in Google Collab also. Okay, but do it in some environment. Don't… if you feel that you are stuck in your own OS, then switch it.
Amit Singh: Got you, got you, got you. Fair enough, fair enough, Paul. Let me try, and I'll come back.
Krish Naik: Okay.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Okay, terrible.
Krish Naik: to some, but… I think Sampath, you go ahead.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Your quadrant tissue, I want to look. Yeah, should I share this thing? Because with the UVicon, I'm able to run, but when I use the Docker.
samapth reddy vummanthala: So it's saying, plant errors and corn errors, so…
Krish Naik: Okay, okay, show me. I am adding onto panelist, yes.
Krish Naik: Next, I think, Mantage, if you are there, Suwash is there.
Mantaaj: My question is not related to this one, I just have one quick question, and meanwhile, Sampat is sharing the screen. So, today, Paul, we were talking about this metadata, right? So, we saw that there were the documents which were created, which you have created it, where we have defined the nodes and…
Mantaaj: the metadata was defined, right, with the key-value pair, but what if in case when we are uploading a document, right? So, do we get all those, kind of… because we get metadata with certain key values.
Mantaaj: But do, so how do we do it in that case when we're uploading a document? Do we add more key values to that?
Krish Naik: Generally, metadata, if I'm talking about, it comes with fewer document types. It's not for every document type, you'll be getting metadata.
Krish Naik: If you're working with .kx, PDF or these type of files, if you have a simple.py file. Markdown file, you don't have metadata in that case.
Mantaaj: You need to build the metadata by yourself.
Mantaaj: Okay.
Krish Naik: Based on certain schema that you will be deciding. It means that you will decide that, okay, I want to keep the text. Probably I showed you something, like, with respect to title, with respect to summary, with respect to total number of characters, all those type of stats, you can keep it.
Krish Naik: I am not… every time you won't be getting metadata, you have to handle it from your own.
Mantaaj: for you to plan with them, or… okay.
Mantaaj: Watted. Okay, that was my only question.
Krish Naik: And you have to plan it in such a way that when you are doing the search operation, like anybody is asking any question or a query, okay, at that particular point of time, how you can use the metadata for performing any type of filtering task.
Mantaaj: You mean to say, those kind of key value players?
Krish Naik: Yes, the key value piece that you will be deciding. On top of that, you will apply the filter. Once the filter is applied, then you have to search lesser number of chunks within the vector tick.
Mantaaj: Otherwise, you have to search the entire vector DB. I hope you get my point.
Mantaaj: I'm getting your point, yes, yeah, yeah.
Krish Naik: Love it. Hmm.
samapth reddy vummanthala: But, yeah.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, high blood, I am too.
Krish Naik: Yes, I think Sampat here, now show me.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, should I show?
Krish Naik: Yeah, yeah. Alright, yeah, start.
Krish Naik: Yes, do the inferencing, I think the server has started.
Krish Naik: Arun, answer if possible, Arun… I need to go answer, if possible. Arun, you can raise your hand.
Krish Naik: Okay, your question is related to, we work with RDAs and data engineering are into data type, okay, row column, okay, how are industrial data analysts need this data?
Krish Naik: For visualization, and yes, that part will remain the same. There won't be many changes there. There will be some type of data warehousing solution.
Krish Naik: Okay, from there, the analyst guys will pick up, and they will pick. There is no change in this part.
Krish Naik: And what happens to the relational database versus docs? Okay, now see, the purpose is different.
Krish Naik: There, you have a different purpose. Working with vector databases, that is a different thing.
Krish Naik: Both the tasks are different. Right now, I feel that in the next 2 to 3 years, majorly, there will be certain solutions, right now, majorly organizations, where they will be integrating, like, NoSQL with VectorDB, SQL with VectorDB, and probably Graph support also.
Krish Naik: Okay, crop support has…
Krish Naik: become also important, I think. But that process will never change. It means that the analyst guys pick up the data from the warehouse, and based on that, they will be creating reports.
Krish Naik: I don't feel. For rack-based solutions, only, that requirement of vector TB. And I was working with Oracle 26S really good. Like, in a single DB, you have every option to work with.
Krish Naik: Okay, show me here.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, should I get that document post?
samapth reddy vummanthala: Readiness section.
Krish Naik: See, if there are some documents, directly make a query.
samapth reddy vummanthala: No, there is no documents that are deleted, so…
Krish Naik: You delete it, then do the upload.
Krish Naik: Go back to the terminal, show me the terminal log.
Krish Naik: Namil is asking, how can we deploy multiple Docker images? If you have multiple Docker images, then you can do the orchestration with Docker Compose.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Also document. No content will be extracted from the document.
Krish Naik: I will come to you, Nabil, okay? Just raise your hand, I will come to you.
Krish Naik: Okay, you're selling 500 internet server, no content could be extracted.
Krish Naik: Created 0 chunks. Now, splitting 19 documents into chunks, because you had 19 pages. Here, you're chunking fail.
Krish Naik: Ivy.
samapth reddy vummanthala: But normal Yubicon is working, so only with the Docker only, I'm facing this issue, when you run… when you run with the Docker.
Krish Naik: Because within the Docker… Right here, because here I feel that your chunks could not be created.
samapth reddy vummanthala: D.K.
Krish Naik: zero chance. That is the first step that I feel.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Earlier, earlier in the morning, I tried, actually, so I got this error, so…
samapth reddy vummanthala: So, earlier this morning is saying, unable to check client server compatibility. So, this was error from the top level.
samapth reddy vummanthala: This collection drive documents is there, but again, on a forbidden response layer.
Krish Naik: Readiness check failed it means.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, good pleasure.
Krish Naik: to VectorDB.
samapth reddy vummanthala: That was…
Krish Naik: Please show it.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, readiness, I have tried. RAG was failing, because uploading documents, RAG collection is failing. So, even I tried to remove the RAG documents from the quadrant, and again, tried to generate.
samapth reddy vummanthala: But,
samapth reddy vummanthala: Anywhere you should, but only with UCon is fine, but I'm not sure with Docker. So, if it works fine only, then I can push to CACD and all the things, right?
Krish Naik: Yes, if the image is working fine in your local, then only you should make the push.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah.
Krish Naik: Okay, now, let's see, go back to the part, because here, no content could be extracted.
Krish Naik: Because 19 documents, that's basically 19 pages, but created… Zero chunks. Now, this part…
Krish Naik: You can log into the image, but again, stop the server.
Krish Naik: Okay, show me the container that is running to a Docker PS iPhone 8.
Krish Naik: Which image is that?
Krish Naik: Okay, the first one, I think. You can take the container ID, you can copy it.
Krish Naik: Container item.
Krish Naik: Okay, alright, here, docker exec.
Krish Naik: EXCC… Space hyphen IT.
Krish Naik: Okay, and then the name of the…
Krish Naik: Image that you have, copied.
Krish Naik: And at the end, write Bash. I think Bash will be there.
Krish Naik: SH, something like deep and SH.
Krish Naik: Yeah, hit enter once. Let's see.
Krish Naik: Okay, the container, is not running, I think you stop the container, start the container once more.
samapth reddy vummanthala: You're right.
Krish Naik: Because in the logs also, I'll be getting the same response, so where exactly…
Krish Naik: You have so many rag project class, even I am.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, because I have, keep on creating the Docker images, and .
Krish Naik: Delete or run, delete, delete, delete. So many things are not required. Select all and delete. Just start the server once more.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Like, they do care about it.
Krish Naik: I am planning to go inside the Docker image, and within that, you… if you run the server, then exactly what happens. We need to check.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Can I remove this one also? So, I'll show the build again one more time.
Krish Naik: Hmm… Here's delete, not a problem.
samapth reddy vummanthala: So, builders are sharing with me.
Krish Naik: remove the building. Right now, the main focus is just go back.
Krish Naik: I'm… first of all, you need to go inside the container, just see the container is running or not.
Krish Naik: Run the container, do the same command, docker build.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Let's start.
samapth reddy vummanthala: There's no doubt.
samapth reddy vummanthala: bring me to follow up.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Should it be?
Krish Naik: Yes.
samapth reddy vummanthala: This quickly completed.
Krish Naik: generally, like, and V, the name of the image.
Krish Naik: Okay, just do one thing. The image is available, no? Let's use Docker run, I think, in that way it will do. Get back.
Krish Naik: Just right here, the image is available.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah. Just do the right docker images and check the image.
Krish Naik: Then I'll simply, do a docker run, space hyphen IT, I think the image name, and then write bash.
samapth reddy vummanthala: No problem.
Krish Naik: Space IT.
Krish Naik: Space.
Krish Naik: FNIT, the name of the image, rag project class.
Krish Naik: rack project class, the name of the image, just pass it, or the image ID also, you can pass it.
samapth reddy vummanthala: AC5, okay, huh? Then, no, you don't need to write rag project class again. At the end, just you have to write bash.
Krish Naik: B-S-H-bash, yes.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Sure, and…
Krish Naik: Aha, enter, enter. If we get error, we will see no? Yes. Now, do an LS here. This is the app structure within that app.
Krish Naik: Well, right now.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Premier Lien Vital is… okay.
Krish Naik: You have to go and actually, like,
Krish Naik: First, go inside the app and do a CDM.
Krish Naik: app, inside an app, here you have your… main.py file.
samapth reddy vummanthala: I'm being limited to the service.
Krish Naik: Because the core file where your chunking mechanism that comes is from…
Krish Naik: This is modular and structured. Okay, fine, do a 3, dot dot, go a step back.
Krish Naik: And try to run the Ubigon command from here. Just see that it's working or not. That Ubigon command. Complete command.
Krish Naik: Really, really, really, like, an… What is the issue?
Krish Naik: You don't remember the command?
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, it's okay.
Krish Naik: Hmm.
Krish Naik: The name of the package, then the name of the folder, then the name of the file.
Krish Naik: Okay, now go back to your here, huh? This one, okay, but I won't… You don't have anything…
Krish Naik: Okay, locally it was, uploading, no? The document was uploading locally.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, yes, it's a normal lease.
Krish Naik: So, in the collection, are there any documents or blank?
samapth reddy vummanthala: No, no hiring mode, so I guess I'd show you that as well.
Krish Naik: If you have removed it, then fine. Because, see, I can make a curl call through here just to do the verification, but if you have nothing, then…
Krish Naik: Making the cull call,
Krish Naik: Because, again, here there is no PDF, so through call call, again, I cannot pass any PDF.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah.
Krish Naik: Like, somewhere, like, try to keep the data inside the Docker image through which I can pass it. These are the only options that you need to check around.
Krish Naik: Like, going inside the docker, I'll be executing the same commands.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Some error is coming.
samapth reddy vummanthala: If I run from inside.
Krish Naik: It is running in 8000 PUT.
Krish Naik: So right now, it's saying that, all right. See, when you run… I think .env file is not there, because of that, it's throwing you there.
Krish Naik: And you cannot access something from the browser, it is not possible. It's running within the Docker.
Krish Naik: You cannot access it in browser.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah.
Krish Naik: Then why you opened the browser?
Krish Naik: I got confused now.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Oh, God.
Krish Naik: Okay, see, here you have not passed the ENVG, so these errors are fine, these are validation errors.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Okay, yeah, yeah.
Krish Naik: Okay, no, there is no issue with this error.
Krish Naik: And you can't open this browser, this is running within the Docker. If you do a mapping operation, then only it can run it in your local browser. Alright, now, because there is no such way, because I can do an implementation
Krish Naik: I will be adding a lot of print statements to debug, that's the only thing that I can think about right now.
Krish Naik: Because I have to exactly in which line it is breaking, that part you need to see, and in your error, directly in the logger, it was coming, that it could not do that chunking. So, that chunking strategy, just have it checked.
Krish Naik: That exactly in the chunking strategy.
Krish Naik: Because at least, because I know the chunks will be created after that embedding happens, so your program is not reaching, till the point of embedding.
Krish Naik: No embedding logs were showed. So, in chunking only, it failed.
Krish Naik: No… I really, like.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Okay, should I run normal UVCon so that it will be…
Krish Naik: In local, you can do it. Whatever telling you local, it's working.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, locally's working. Docker only? Yeah, I'm seeing the issues.
Krish Naik: Okay, shh, in local, first of all, shown, you're good.
Krish Naik: Have you changed any parentheses somewhere?
samapth reddy vummanthala: Parameters, because actually.
Krish Naik: Not parameters parallel to this.
samapth reddy vummanthala: No, like.
Krish Naik: file path and anything. If you have changed, then it will fail.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Nothing, you know, car-wise, no. Only because it's building here, then I created a build, and then he created build.
Krish Naik: Okay, show me the local one. I need to really look into that.
Krish Naik: APIT is fine, that's not the deal.
Krish Naik: You'll be gone and show me here by uploading the PDF quickly.
Krish Naik: Generally, it should not happen, but sometimes…
samapth reddy vummanthala: Nope.
samapth reddy vummanthala: New York!
samapth reddy vummanthala: Nichols.
Krish Naik: Santosh, if you have, I will just add you just…
Santosh Umargi: Hello?
Krish Naik: Yes, I'm pushing.
Santosh Umargi: Yeah, yeah, I'm, I tried in the, this, no, VS Code, that same code.
Krish Naik: Here, also, you were getting a 500 error.
Krish Naik: You are telling me local it is working?
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, I have done, that's what,
samapth reddy vummanthala: This is after some time, then this error got in the… And Ram Dakhmet has created.
Krish Naik: See, locally, first, make it work. And local only, it is not working.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Actually, I verified. See, the apps are verified. Locally work, then I immediately build image, then I run.
Krish Naik: How it will feel now, that's the main question.
Krish Naik: It doesn't happen with programs.
Krish Naik: Because here only it fails, so for sure in the Docker image it will fail.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Fair enough.
samapth reddy vummanthala: A simplified or so later.
Krish Naik: Yes.
Krish Naik: You go ahead. Santosh?
Santosh Umargi: Yeah, I'm getting that, all, faithfulness 1 and, relevancy 1.
Krish Naik: How many questions do you have passed?
Santosh Umargi: Same, like, you shared, no, that 5e questions.
Krish Naik: Okay, in your case, it's fine. It's the evaluation results, nothing that can… again, the document that you have used, it matters on that also.
Santosh Umargi: Yeah, yeah, okay.
Santosh Umargi: Okay, okay, got it, yeah.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Oh, now it is, it's cool.
Krish Naik: Okay, now in that document image, now this is, all right. Pass the same PDF, last time, that track PDF we were sharing?
samapth reddy vummanthala: Okay. Yes.
Krish Naik: start the Docker.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Or should rest on another terminal?
Krish Naik: Yes.
Krish Naik: Non-breaking object, server restart.
samapth reddy vummanthala: No, no.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Now, utility, which one, actually? No, both are running, right?
Krish Naik: Take directly the upload route, don't take other routes.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Now, shall I delete it or let it be the documents and everything?
Krish Naik: No, no, click on everything.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Everything's already there, right? So that's what.
Krish Naik: Let me see the logs here.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, this is from Guard.
Krish Naik: The pay didn't got hit only. In the other tab, is any other instance of UVCon running?
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, this is locally.
Krish Naik: Well, close this one, close this one, otherwise how we will access it.
Krish Naik: Try to reload the page and check that.
Krish Naik: Here, it will not come. Again, you have to process the request.
Krish Naik: Just click on execute.
Krish Naik: Try it out, click on try it out, again, upload the doc.
Krish Naik: Anybody else want to share their screen, please let me know.
Suyash Sharma: Hi, Paul, Suha just said, I have some small couple of questions.
Krish Naik: Yes, please wait.
Suyash Sharma: Yeah. My first question is, like, we will… will there be some kind of exercise where we will, take input as a database source and then use it…
Krish Naik: project it is there, no.
Suyash Sharma: Okay.
Suyash Sharma: And my second question is, like, a friend, I mean, some colleagues of mine, they just built this rag, I mean, simple…
Suyash Sharma: a PDF upload, and then trying to analyze the PDF, and they were using, like, Azure AI, but, like, they… most of them, like, did not know what exactly is there. So, my question is, like, in a production-ready environment, what exactly things are there? I mean.
Suyash Sharma: The parameter that we see for creating an application, measurably.
Krish Naik: Parameters, you really, need to look into the response of the rack.
Krish Naik: That is where, like, your retrieval results and your generation results, these two things you need to keep a track on.
Krish Naik: The most important thing.
Krish Naik: Building ragilihi.
Krish Naik: But maintaining that, RAG, okay, with a proper solution, that is the main pain point.
Krish Naik: You need to always track the metrics for every type of response which the user is passing.
Krish Naik: Based on the query, how the retriever is working, are you getting the correct retrieve context or not? Those things you have to plan.
Suyash Sharma: Got it, good.
Suyash Sharma: Yeah, and, like, my last question is, like, previously, I sent you, like, an email, as I'm in discussion previous class, of my assumes. Did you got a chance to check on that?
Krish Naik: The resume, till now, I have not picked up anybody, only I think I've responded. That part, I will do it this way.
Krish Naik: much more time, a lot of extra classes I take.
Suyash Sharma: I got it. Thank you so much.
samapth reddy vummanthala: So, first is God warning, so just a version check something.
samapth reddy vummanthala: So…
Krish Naik: to check client-server compatibility. Yeah. All this is coming from the vector store file, and quadrant connected embedding model, this is done. Okay, fine, but here, error is…
Krish Naik: Response thing, initialize with 1536.
Krish Naik: And it's 403 want to be done, raw error is forbidden.
Krish Naik: Now, this error is coming from the vector store file, as I can see here.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, from 400, so client… so, client server community. Server is fine.
Krish Naik: this error is coming from your vector store, now I'm thinking that you're… credentials for, embedding.
Krish Naik: Because it's telling, creating, collection rag document. Just check, in quadrant whether rag underscore document got created or not.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, it is created, so… yes, no. But we are now deleted, right?
samapth reddy vummanthala: So right now, I think it will be created, no? If it is created? Yeah, yes ma'am.
Krish Naik: Yes.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Because it's created with local, locally when we run, right? So at that time it's created.
Krish Naik: Okay, now it's failing. I feel that you are working with Gemini.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah.
Krish Naik: Now, check the dimension size. By default, Gemini pickup 30072 dimensions.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Okay, and here you have passed 1536. Error was coming, so I downgraded, so 1536, so…
Krish Naik: This is just, you have created a collection, but inside that, nothing has gone. So, I'm feeling that the, there is some mismatch with diamond emitting dimensions.
Krish Naik: But here, okay, here I can see some embeddings are there.
Krish Naik: Alright, now go back, go back, total how many? This is test, project, go back, go back, there, show me the UI. In the collection, how many data points are there?
samapth reddy vummanthala: data points.
samapth reddy vummanthala: This is… we'll close, right?
Krish Naik: Quadrant TY. In the quadrant TY, it will show you, no?
Krish Naik: How many data points.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Okay.
Krish Naik: Click on Cluster EY, Cluster EY.
Krish Naik: Click on Cluster UI.
Krish Naik: Where they could be showing?
Krish Naik: Okay, total 66 data points.
Krish Naik: tagged when it means that the embedding part is also working.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, go back to the logs.
Krish Naik: Okay, so I will take creating collections, error, processing the document on…
Krish Naik: Error processing, the document unexpected response. Now, this part really, like.
Krish Naik: Api routes, because finally, the error which is coming, it is coming from this vector store has done this document route, okay?
Krish Naik: unexpected response. Go to the documents.
Krish Naik: Route 1.
Krish Naik: Open it in script, yes. Documents.
Krish Naik: Also, really, like, you have to, yes, within app routes.
Krish Naik: Click on app.
Krish Naik: Inside that, you have your API.
Krish Naik: Inside that, you have your routes.
Krish Naik: Okay, document.py. Now, this is where it is failing.
Krish Naik: Okay, now, here, I haven't kept a lot of statement, but
Krish Naik: invalid, processing type, only two types of, responses that I have kept.
Krish Naik: Cost slash upload text, and upload, scroll down.
Krish Naik: Okay, final name is required, validate, okay, now this validation is done. Now, from here, I'm calling the document processor, process upload, this part is done. Scroll down, scroll down.
Krish Naik: Yes, so the vector store service, add documents is done, log that info.
Krish Naik: Successfully processed the chunks, then coming to…
Krish Naik: Message, file name, chunks created, this will be returned. I think in your case, this was not returned, no?
Krish Naik: This information, and show me the logs once.
Krish Naik: Error processing the document, directly unexpected response, 403 came. Oh, let's go back.
Krish Naik: The error is coming from this route, in the documents, the final error.
Krish Naik: Now, this part, really, like, debugging the stuff.
Krish Naik: Because if I push the entire code to GitHub and share with me.
Krish Naik: Because, really, like, if in my system it works now, then again it can be a problem.
Krish Naik: Like, exactly to identify. It happens, like.
Krish Naik: But I feel that you were working with Gemini, okay? And, alright, don't give me the Gemini key, I don't need the Gemini key, but .
samapth reddy vummanthala: This is, here, actually, I have the deposit here.
Krish Naik: Okay, and ENV file manually you have created in the root folder.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, GitHub, and I ignored I mentioned methods.
Krish Naik: Okay, fine. Okay, and then, share me this report.
Krish Naik: Without taking a clone, it's hard for me to exactly debug him.
samapth reddy vummanthala: Yeah, sure.
Krish Naik: No, right. No more two panelists. Naga, I have added you. Jagapati, Nabil, then, Saurabh, everybody I have unmuted. One by one, you guys can go ahead.
NABEEL AHMED: Hi, Paul.
Krish Naik: Yes.
NABEEL AHMED: Yeah, actually, I'm working on one of my projects where I'm using the three Docker files, and that is one for PG SQL, one for Redis, one for main port code. So, how can I deploying all these three files in once, like, they are communicating with each other? Redis is storing the cache, and PG SQL is storing the user detail.
Krish Naik: It doesn't matter, you can use Docker Compose, no? That is the purpose of using Docker Compose, the orchestration of my.
NABEEL AHMED: Yeah.
Krish Naik: Gotcha.
Krish Naik: Yeah, I can, like, locally it is working, but I want to deploy on the, like, AWS. In those type of cases, AWS, use AWS target.
NABEEL AHMED: It's par… target, yeah, okay.
Krish Naik: Okay, that is the main service.
NABEEL AHMED: Okay, okay. Yeah, then I will explore, and I'll come to you if I get any, like, anything you think I want to discuss. Yeah, that's it from myself.
Krish Naik: No, right now, Bill.
Naga: Paul, I have a question, so, when I'm trying to…
Naga: data generator questions, no matter what key I use, it… even I reduce this to number of questions.
Krish Naik: If it's sending too many requests, it means that your API issue is there. Nothing done.
Naga: I haven't.
Krish Naik: I do.
Naga: No, no, but if we don't know the solution, we are completely stuck, right? I mean, this open API key, I changed 4 keys, different keys, just within one hour. Nothing is working. Like, why it's the case?
Krish Naik: Avoid the scale seek, the API is blocking, because multiple requests, you are making it.
Krish Naik: What you can do, you can add some type of delay, probably.
Krish Naik: Okay, now again, now you have to change the code in the module level.
Krish Naik: Because, now the portion comes, it's tire-based. Okay, now, generally in the lower tire, you cannot make a lot of requests, though you might.
Naga: If I add some money into this, will it go through? Like, I'm just trying to understand. See, this is,
Naga: OpenAI keys, yeah, come on. Yeah, here, right. So, if I add money into this, do you think it will go?
Krish Naik: How much credit you have, first of all, just show me. At least you need more than $2.
Krish Naik: Show me that.
Krish Naik: Billy, but click on Billy. Click on Billy.
Naga: Bing… What's the billing here, sir, usage…
Krish Naik: Billing, billing, billing, billing on top, top, top, on top, top. No, no, no, no, no. Okay, here also you will be getting. So here you have zero credits, so how it will work?
Naga: So, I had some… I had a credit card, so how many dollars should I put into this?
Krish Naik: See, putting dollars is not the main thing. You can work with Gemini also.
Krish Naik: I have shown you the code. Do the changes, it's not necessary. If you want, you can take, I think, minimum $6 recharge that you can do.
Naga: Saves dollars, okay, so it will…
Naga: Again, so which is better to use? Is it better to use the.
Krish Naik: There is nothing better. It's totally one's preference.
Naga: So Gemini is completely free?
Krish Naik: Not completely. There are daily limits.
Mudassar Hakim: Here, dear, it's there. Paul, can you let me share my screen? I'll just…
Krish Naik: Yes, just clicked, .
Naga: So… So you want me to switch to Germany, or should I add some money.
Krish Naik: I don't want, whichever way you want, if you want to get the credits, get the credits, use OpenAI. If you want to switch to Gemini, the same thing. Okay.
Naga: Let me explain something.
Krish Naik: Again, repeated the same thing. Nothing is free.
Naga: There are daily limits.
Naga: Daily limits.
Krish Naik: Yes, once you hit the limit, done.
Naga: Okay, I will add some money in this account.
Krish Naik: In Gemini, also, you can add a credit card. In that way, you can come from the free track to tire 1, Tire 2, Tire 3 in that way.
Naga: Okay.
Krish Naik: Alright, yes, I can see now on the screen.
Mudassar Hakim: Yeah, yeah, so I just ran the thing, and I just want to take… get your feedback. So I've used a different PDF, just for starters. I will eventually take more. I've taken a very small PDF, just to understand.
Krish Naik: Only that one page.
Mudassar Hakim: Only one page. Yeah, that's right.
Mudassar Hakim: And the questions are pretty straightforward. These are my eval questions.
Mudassar Hakim: Okay.
Krish Naik: Alright.
Mudassar Hakim: Now, post-processing, this is the result.
Mudassar Hakim: Which comes to faithfulness around 70.
Krish Naik: Alright, the faithfulness around… that is, relevancy and both things. Faithfulness, okay, know where there is a similar value.
Krish Naik: Alright, now, like, really, if I check chunk 512, that is performing better with respect to response times.
Krish Naik: The faithfulness was dropped.
Krish Naik: To 6.0, part relegant sales high this time.
Krish Naik: In your case, chunk 128 looks good, much better, I can say.
Krish Naik: Because both 7070 is there. In other places, there is no 70.
Mudassar Hakim: Sorry.
Krish Naik: See, really, like, these values will drop if you test with the bigger dogs, but, just be sure you should have high… first priority should go to faithfulness, the second priority will go to relevance, and the third priority will go to response time.
Mudassar Hakim: That is agreed, for sure.
Mudassar Hakim: For sure. And also, needless to say, there was a few tweaking of the code also, which I have done, you know, and I hope that is going in the right direction. Oh, yeah, by the way, a different…
Jagapathi: to different.
Mudassar Hakim: model also. I use a turbo. I did not use a…
Krish Naik: 8.5 is good.
Mudassar Hakim: Yeah, I used a turbo.
Mudassar Hakim: And so, with this approach, then I start adding a bigger document and see how things work, right?
Krish Naik: Actually, the approach that everyone takes, for example, they have 10,000 documents, so on top of 100 documents, they do the test day.
Krish Naik: That is the idea.
Mudassar Hakim: Okay.
Krish Naik: Okay, it means that on a subset of your data, so really, like, subset means at least, like, 5% of the data, or at least, it should be more than 2% of the data that you should test.
Mudassar Hakim: But again, like, it totally depends upon the total size of the data. If you have petabytes, that 2% also becomes very big. But take at least, because I feel that.
Krish Naik: At least 10 to 15 documents that you can take in.
Mudassar Hakim: Uber document you shared, and because I had pretty much big. It, like.
Krish Naik: Yes, this is a bigger one.
Mudassar Hakim: Okay, okay. So I didn't know if I should start with 300 documents, that's why I started.
Krish Naik: No, no, no, no, leave it. Use a smaller one.
Mudassar Hakim: Can you just give me a ballpark number with a smaller, how many pages should I try with?
Krish Naik: 10 pages at least.
Mudassar Hakim: I'll try it with her and share the response.
Krish Naik: Once you start working with bigger documents, you will see that the faithfulness and few values will drop, actually.
Mudassar Hakim: Yeah, yep, yep, yup, yep. Okay, thanks.
saurabh verma: Yeah, Paul, can you please, add me to the panel list to share my screen?
Krish Naik: I have added you to the panelists. Kodali, Purna Chan, Sari were also unmuted.
Krish Naik: Jagopathy, you are also unmuted. Jagopathy, if you have questions, please go ahead.
Krish Naik: Jagaphat, you want to share the screen? Fine. I have added you two panelists.
Krish Naik: Volt.
Krish Naik: Aramani, I think your question is taken.
Krish Naik: Yes?
Armani, Bhagwan Das: Yes, you're taken, actually.
Krish Naik: Okay, alright.
Armani, Bhagwan Das: But keep on… keep it in aisle, and I'll go on mute, but if anything is there…
Krish Naik: Okay, okay, fine print.
saurabh verma: all…
Krish Naik: All right.
saurabh verma: Getting those here?
Krish Naik: Yes, like, first, who was sharing the screen with AWS error? Yes, so I'm looking into, AWS, sorry, yes, sorry, your screen, GitHub, page I'm looking into.
saurabh verma: So yesterday, we had done, 95% of it, so we had to just, do the app service, right? So, I'll show this thing. This, I had, set up the Rack UA app service, okay?
Krish Naik: Alright.
saurabh verma: And and this also, I updated the name in the file, the deploy.yml, the name also is the same, okay?
Krish Naik: Okay?
saurabh verma: this one. The, my two questions. One is.
saurabh verma: In the settings, secret key in GitHub, the value of that, key is this, no? We should set.
Krish Naik: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, not this guy.
Krish Naik: The name comes with ECR Access Rule.
saurabh verma: Sorry, which name.
Krish Naik: Not this one, not this one.
saurabh verma: Okay, so I should go to IM.
Krish Naik: No, no, not I am. So generally, when you are creating, it shows you, see, AR and ECR access rules, this is the one.
saurabh verma: So, this hole… hole I should take.
Krish Naik: Yes.
saurabh verma: Okay? I take this… And then… I go here… I have this here.
saurabh verma: And here, in this… I pasted here, right?
Krish Naik: Yes, yes.
saurabh verma: Okay.
saurabh verma: I will do this, and meanwhile, you can talk.
Krish Naik: All looked fine.
Krish Naik: Yes, Jennifer T. Yes.
Kodali Purna Chand: Paul, can you make me a presenter?
Krish Naik: Okay, yes, I will add you to presentation, to panelists, yes.
Krish Naik: Javati… Tell me the issue.
Kodali Purna Chand: Or let me know.
Kodali Purna Chand: Very nice.
Krish Naik: Jagapati, I cannot, get your audio.
Krish Naik: No audio from inside.
Kodali Purna Chand: While I'm sharing my screen, let me know whenever you want me to speak.
Krish Naik: Okay, yes, I think you're gonna go ahead, there is no audio from Jagavake's site, yes.
Krish Naik: So… Yes, already in your VNV, you have done PipShole index score, okay?
Kodali Purna Chand: So if this goes all right, there's also…
Kodali Purna Chand: This is something I had to do with.
Kodali Purna Chand: then this was alright. This one also… Everything is working fine.
Kodali Purna Chand: But I'm not getting the output. The other thing I wanted to highlight.
Kodali Purna Chand: I have uploaded my own document.
Kodali Purna Chand: Instead of the… One, instead of taking it from the website.
Kodali Purna Chand: So, I'm not… I'm not using this.
Kodali Purna Chand: So, I'm basically… I've kept the document in this particular folder.
Kodali Purna Chand: this document.
Krish Naik: And right?
Kodali Purna Chand: So, Dan, good questions?
Kodali Purna Chand: And that's asking it to generate.
Kodali Purna Chand: Set up evaluations…
Kodali Purna Chand: In most of the places, I had to redeploy, rewrite the code, so whatever is commented is original code, and what I'm putting here is the proposed.
Krish Naik: Yes, yes, the imports have changed. There was a change in the liability, that's why.
Kodali Purna Chand: So then, on this, everything, there's no error, but I'm not getting the output.
Krish Naik: There is no errors, show me, show me, show me.
Krish Naik: The return total time… So, where there are print statements is the return, I can see.
Krish Naik: But exactly where you are calling that return.
Kodali Purna Chand: Okay.
Krish Naik: There are no print statements only, then how we will get that?
Kodali Purna Chand: Okay, okay, okay.
Krish Naik: Please compare with the original notebook. You will see at the end, there are print statements which are attached, and right now, here I can see you have make it commented. There has to be print statements. Without the print, how it will work?
Kodali Purna Chand: Right, okay, I got that there.
Kodali Purna Chand: Okay. The other thing, regarding the project that you had given, that was… I could complete all those flows, so there's no issue. Only piece of information I wanted to share is that I am on the free plan, and I could create the apprunner
Kodali Purna Chand: Volle.
Krish Naik: So, in your case, it got created.
Kodali Purna Chand: Yeah, so I could do the complete TF2.
Krish Naik: Alright, fine. But, at least I think you have added some type of payment No, with your…
Kodali Purna Chand: Yes, nothing. I'm on the free plan of $200, so I've already consumed about, $90… $50.
Krish Naik: Many people, like yesterday, at least you need some type of payment verification, then it works. In your case.
Kodali Purna Chand: I was getting ready for it, but…
Krish Naik: In the time.
Kodali Purna Chand: That's for it, so…
Krish Naik: All right.
Kodali Purna Chand: Okay, okay, thanks.
Krish Naik: Yes, Jagapati, now I'm looking into your screen. Tell me the problem or write in chat somewhere.
Krish Naik: Because now I'm looking into your app runner screen.
Krish Naik: You want to do a rebuild, okay?
Krish Naik: Anybody else want to share their screen, they can start.
Krish Naik: I think there is nobody else.
Amit Singh: Paul, sir, Ramit here again. I signed up in the Lightning, I created my setup, now what to do? I mean, it's a…
Amit Singh: Greenfield completely right now.
Krish Naik: greenfield wind?
Amit Singh: I was in… it's all blank right now.
Krish Naik: Okay, okay.
Amit Singh: I do a Git clone.
Krish Naik: You are in the panelists, start sharing.
Amit Singh: Yeah.
Krish Naik: No, no, no, here you have to clone the repo.
Amit Singh: That is what happens. So I go to Lake Tabunal.
Krish Naik: to do the… no, no, no, no, no. You have to open the preference settings, like Ctrl-Shift-P. If you are on Windows, I think that is okay.
Amit Singh: Okay, Ctrl-Shift-P.
Amit Singh: So this perplexity opens up… no, no, actually, I have to go to settings, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Krish Naik: Generally, the shortcut is Ctrl-Shift-P in any one. No, you are not audible, Jagapati. You are not audible.
Krish Naik: Or logically, you have to, right here, clone, CLONE.
Krish Naik: Git clone, hit enter.
Krish Naik: Pay the rippling.
Krish Naik: No, not the recursive, use the first option.
Amit Singh: Yeah, yeah, this one only.
Krish Naik: The first one only git clone?
Krish Naik: Now paste the report.
Amit Singh: Cool.
Krish Naik: How many tabs we have opened.
Amit Singh: Yeah, I have, like, I have got to study all that.
Amit Singh: So, I go back to…
Krish Naik: Boom.
Krish Naik: No.
Amit Singh: Cool.
Krish Naik: Take the RAG UA class one, this is the project one.
Amit Singh: Class 1.
Krish Naik: Yes.
Amit Singh: So, do I go to Khan? I got confused, because I was working with this, and then I forked my repo yesterday, looking at the later half of the recording, and then…
Krish Naik: Hmm.
Amit Singh: That class came.
Amit Singh: I was not working with class initially when I was… when I created the project.
Krish Naik: Okay…
Amit Singh: So, very true.
Amit Singh: But I do have the class stored as a folder on my desktop.
Krish Naik: Just take that, repo and clone it.
Amit Singh: From there, you can take it.
Krish Naik: Otherwise, just go to my rep one from there, I'll go to repos, and just take that one. It will work.
Amit Singh: So, I go to geography.
Amit Singh: This is your report, right?
Krish Naik: Now click on my name, that's Sorang Shapalis there, click on that.
Krish Naik: Click on that, then you have to… no, no, here you will see the commits, actually. The top one, where it's there.
Amit Singh: This one.
Krish Naik: Then click on My Repos, Repositories 161 is there, click on that.
Krish Naik: Repository 161 below the name, on top.
Amit Singh: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Krish Naik: repos, huh?
Krish Naik: Click that, then you will see, here, scroll down, track project class, click on this one.
Amit Singh: Got you, got you, got you, okay.
Krish Naik: Take the link, and do the cloning operation. No, no, no, no, take code, green color button.
Amit Singh: Or green color, whatever. Yeah, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, yeah, yeah, I know.
Krish Naik: It should be at the end, yeah. Now go back and paste it there.
Krish Naik: Again, Ctrl-Shift-P, do it, and right-click.
Krish Naik: Hit enter.
Krish Naik: Okay, could you allow JB audio? What is JB audio?
Krish Naik: I have, I kept on getting in progress on JB Audio, alright, Sharmoni, happy weekend. Can you allow JB Audio? What is JB Audio?
Krish Naik: I have no idea what is JB audio.
Krish Naik: Okay, you have another account, fine, fine, fine, I got it, got, got it.
Amit Singh: Okay, drop…
Krish Naik: I will notify.
Amit Singh: So, right, to the parent workspace.
Amit Singh: Should I add this to the workspace?
Krish Naik: No, no, no, open it here, only open in new window, or open it here, doesn't matter so much.
Amit Singh: Okay, cool.
Krish Naik: Cisco.
Krish Naik: Alright, yeah, that's the thing, sir.
JB: Paul.
Krish Naik: Hmm.
JB: Yeah, I'll be speaking from JB and sharing screen from JBati, so…
Krish Naik: Okay, fine, fine, fine, got it, no.
JB: Yes, proceed.
Krish Naik: Are you sure?
Krish Naik: Here, open the terminal amid, and run that docker build command.
Amit Singh: Yes, yeah, okay.
Krish Naik: Yes, Jagavati, now I'm looking into your screen.
JB: Yeah, so I kept on getting this error since yesterday.
Krish Naik: failed, don't say fail, so why it is getting failed, tell me that.
Krish Naik: It means that you have to look into application logs, or GitHub actions, so where it is failing.
JB: Where can I see the logs here?
Krish Naik: Go below, there are two level of logs, the deployment logs and the application logs. Just scroll down.
Krish Naik: Fail to deploy your application image, image pulled from your application. Okay, alright. This is the first level. Fine.
Krish Naik: Look into the other logs also.
JB: You mean application logs?
Krish Naik: Application is not started only, I think, so it will be blank. Click on application and just show me if something is there.
JB: Well, it didn't even.
Krish Naik: Okay, here it came, no. Simply, errors are here.
JB: Oh, okay, okay, I didn't look into this.
Krish Naik: This is, like, Python error. You are getting from settings… Okay, vector store, identic validator…
Krish Naik: Some validation error is coming in your case.
Krish Naik: Because this is the actual Python level, if it fails here, it won't work there.
Krish Naik: Go at the top, just see at the top from where exactly it started.
JB: It isn't supposed to get failed at image creation level itself.
Krish Naik: No, no, no. Image creation, I cannot say, because here, if I look into your application, I started.
Krish Naik: If the application has started, it means that this is a Python error that you got, and the error is coming from UVON line number 7.
Krish Naik: Okay, so it's inside the core package, but scroll down, let's see below exactly where it's getting.
Krish Naik: UVCon server.py, get loop factory, okay? Scroll down, scroll down, down, down, down.
Krish Naik: Okay, now, here, if you look into in our application, from app.piroutes import documents line number 11.
Krish Naik: Okay, and ride number, get settings.
Krish Naik: I think it's not able to get the settings. Because of that, you can see pirate error, GeminiKey, Quadrant URL, and those things are missing. Because your ENV file is not getting recognized.
Krish Naik: Have you passed these things inside the GitHub secrets?
JB: Yeah, of course I did. Let me see what you will.
Krish Naik: Show me the GitHub secrets part.
Krish Naik: Click on Settings, yes, then… This one?
Krish Naik: Here I can see Gemini 12345678, alright.
Krish Naik: Okay, okay, down, show me your CI.Y.
Krish Naik: If you have changed something, have you changed other scripts?
JB: Oh, no, no, nothing.
Krish Naik: So you have to change the other scripts also, no, if you're changing the Gemini key.
JB: Yeah, GeminiK, I changed it. I mean, I'm using GeminiK since… even to run locally as well.
Krish Naik: No, no, no, I'm telling you, in the code, have you changed? In the CD, if you look into the script, there will be a part where you'll be loading OpenAI.
Krish Naik: Variables. That part, have you changed?
JB: Yeah, yeah, I did change.
Krish Naik: Okay, show me that part.
Krish Naik: Because the main error that I can see here, there it's not getting recognized, so…
Krish Naik: Rather than rerunning, try to make a commit and do the deployment.
JB: I made a spell mistake, I believe.
Krish Naik: Jake one.
JB: Yo… It's… I gave the wrong spelling. I think that might be causing issue, is it?
Krish Naik: It's clear.
JB: Absolutely.
Krish Naik: Because it's really hard to say in CICD pipelines.
JB: Aren't…
Krish Naik: So now the main error was, as I looked in the log, it was for, the environment variables were not coming.
JB: Yeah, one statistic…
JB: Also, Paul, is it not supposed to create automatically the app creation? That's what we're…
Krish Naik: Yes, automatically it will create.
Krish Naik: Generally, like, once you have done, you have the ECR access rules, so automatically it can be done.
Krish Naik: But if you don't have that access role, manually you can create, then even you don't need to open the AppRunner page also.
JB: I think I did change, let me push the code.
Krish Naik: Okay.
Amit Singh: Thanks, Paul, so the build happened.
Amit Singh: If I go to my Docker… can you see my Docker thing? Screen? Docker desktop?
Krish Naik: Yes.
Amit Singh: Which is the build? I mean, how…
Amit Singh: How do we recognize, like, the last 10?
Amit Singh: The first one.
Krish Naik: Don't go to build, go to Images and Containers.
Amit Singh: Okay, this one.
Krish Naik: This is the image that you have built in your local, probably, like…
Krish Naik: This is your local, so right now I cannot see any RAG1, so I think you have deleted it.
Amit Singh: No, I didn't delete anything. I just…
Krish Naik: Click on containers. Your image was not getting built only, so how it will show in the image?
Krish Naik: I feel. Yes. There are no… nothing related to the RAC budget, so your image was not getting built, so it is not available here.
Amit Singh: Oh, I see, this is linked to the local one.
Krish Naik: Yes, this is Local Docker.
Amit Singh: Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. So it will not come here at all?
Krish Naik: It will come, it will not come. You have to upload the image to Docker Hub, and then from Docker Hub, you pull it in your local machine.
Amit Singh: Okay, how to do that, then?
Amit Singh: Can you…
Krish Naik: just search in ChatGPT how to upload an image. You have to create a account there. Okay, free, it's completely free. It's just like ECR.
Krish Naik: every cloud has a specific one, like ECR in Google, it's called Artifact Registry, the same thing. Dockerf is free. You have to create an account, push the image, so right now.
Krish Naik: I feel that you already have an account in Docker, as I can see your name A on the top. You have to log into your account, okay, and then you have to push the image from your local.
Krish Naik: Okay, now this is your account, so open the browser, and from there.
Krish Naik: this image which has been created, here you have to do a Docker login, you have to do the account authentication, and I think you can push.
Amit Singh: So, just tell me, I mean, I'll do a chat JP.
Krish Naik: See, simple steps.
Amit Singh: a little bit of…
Krish Naik: The main topic is how to push
Krish Naik: a Docker image from my local machine to Docker Hub.
Amit Singh: Mom.
Amit Singh: local image.
Krish Naik: from my local image to Docker Hub.
Amit Singh: How to push my local image from…
Amit Singh: But my image is on Lightning, no, it's on cloud, right? It's not on my desktop.
Krish Naik: So, it is local there, no?
Krish Naik: See, right now, Lightning is your local, so from there, you will push to Docker app. Then from Docker app, you will bring to your own local piece.
Amit Singh: So, kind of downloading, right, from Docker Hub.
Krish Naik: Yes, yes.
Amit Singh: Download onto my machine, right?
Krish Naik: You will just pull the image. Once you have your repo, then you will just, you will do a Docker pull, and the name of the image that you are uploading.
Amit Singh: Okay, okay, okay. Can you just, like, write this, this thing just, and send it to me, or I'll look at the YouTube videos?
Amit Singh: Of Nana.
Krish Naik: to push, and just wait, let me see if I get any info.
Amit Singh: I mean, I'll do that, after a break, I'll sit with it.
Krish Naik: Osh… book,
saurabh verma: Paul, can I share my screen?
Krish Naik: Yes, you can. You're already there in.
saurabh verma: Yeah, yeah.
Krish Naik: list, so start sharing.
Krish Naik: How to push Docker image to Docker, I think there is…
Amit Singh: Clothing range.
Amit Singh: I mean, I've got to study that and do it.
Krish Naik: comes to Docker.
saurabh verma: So, boy…
Krish Naik: Hmm.
Krish Naik: Just wait and look, getting the blog for him. Yeah, yeah. Build and push your first image, I think this should work, the official Docker one.
Krish Naik: Yes, this is the Docker community.
Krish Naik: Oh, no, not this page, just tweet and…
Krish Naik: These are all the steps which are mentioned, even with the video. I think Amit, it will be helpful to you.
Krish Naik: I have shared the link.
Amit Singh: Oh, goodness.
Krish Naik: link.
Amit Singh: Thank you, thank you, Paul. Thanks, Aden.
Krish Naik: Alright, yes, now I'm looking into Saurabh Skills.
saurabh verma: Yeah. So, this has got, deployed.
Krish Naik: Alright.
saurabh verma: Okay, now, my question is, sorry for asking a very, very silly question. Now, to access the URL, how to access that, the application.
Krish Naik: Shane will check the logs, check the logs, go up, scroll up, scroll up, scroll up, yes, here you got no.
Krish Naik: App Service URL, huh?
saurabh verma: Yeah, so I did that.
Krish Naik: click on that.
Krish Naik: Then, right slash drop.
saurabh verma: Flesh.
Krish Naik: Docs.
saurabh verma: Yeah, so this has come.
Krish Naik: Yes.
saurabh verma: Right, right. Okay, great, great. Okay.
saurabh verma: Fine. So I think this is done, now, everything is set. So… Okay.
Krish Naik: And delete everything, otherwise you will be charged, that's why.
saurabh verma: Yeah, yeah, yesterday I had paused it, but then I thought I'd better delete it.
Krish Naik: Delete it, don't pause.
Krish Naik: Here, don't fall.
saurabh verma: Okay, I'll do that. But thanks for all your help and patience.
Krish Naik: Right, so…
saurabh verma: You can remove me now.
Krish Naik: Okay.
JB: Paul, yeah, it is still polling, waiting for.
Krish Naik: Yes, yes, it will wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait till, like, I know in 2025 it goes.
Krish Naik: It takes 5 minutes, you have to wait.
JB: In my previous attempts, it is failing at that date of that ninth instance… attempt.
Krish Naik: Okay, okay, let's see.
Krish Naik: Hmm.
Amit Singh: You got your surfaces one?
Krish Naik: Click on that service URL. AppRunner Service Arm. Click on that.
JB: Finally.
Krish Naik: You were using the wrong file, my friend.
Krish Naik: You are using the wrong flag.
Krish Naik: Which file you have picked up? The first project, you have not used that rack, and you end it, I think, and there you have picked up the wrong file. That's why you are getting that static slash index.html in it.
Krish Naik: You can work with the docs, though, but the UI won't be available.
Krish Naik: You can work with SlashDocs, okay, because that, just check, I think SlashDocs is opening, no?
Krish Naik: So, yes, it is… Nope.
JB: Yeah, you're right, like, what the… what you mean by file? Yeah, I'm working on the… not yesterday's, the previous weeks.
Krish Naik: That one, if you test it, then. Because right now, in the code, there is no static folder, but the routes are there.
JB: Oh, I'm getting some error.
Krish Naik: This is with respect to your, dimensions. Existing quadrant collection is configured for dense vectors with 1536 selected, and you are using Gemini, I think.
Krish Naik: In Gemini 9, for the embedding creation, you have to very specifically set that
Krish Naik: Okay, or, I think force recreate option is there, just go back and look into that.
Krish Naik: Go below, go below, go below. Look into the error first, what is written? Read the complete error.
JB: Yeah, yeah, I got it. So, 1536 is configured, expecting that Oh, there we are…
Krish Naik: Yes. Okay, now, if you want to recreate the collection, set force recreate parameter is equal to true. Copy that parameter, and paste it there.
Krish Naik: I think, that force recreate is equal to true, it will be overwritten. Just check.
JB: Amazing.
Krish Naik: create even I have not tested, that's why. You can check, because I know it's a damage genera.
JB: Way to set that parameter.
Krish Naik: within your API call, in the body of the call placeset.
JB: between the boys.
Krish Naik: What do you have? Okay, here, go above, go above.
Krish Naik: Gobo.
JB: Above one, okay.
Krish Naik: Top, top, top, top, top, top, let me see, is there a route available? Document is here, close this route, close this one. Go below, let me check the other route.
Krish Naik: Do I have a… I don't think document info is there, document collection is there?
Krish Naik: Okay, because in your, code, you have to do that particular setting, I think.
Krish Naik: You don't have a route right now to update the collection. I have not added any such routes. Now, manually, you have to do the changes in the code only.
JB: So I'm expected to have parameters like this, right?
Krish Naik: No, in your code, you have to just change the embedding dimension. When you are creating the embedding, just be sure they are up.
Krish Naik: 1536, okay? Or, delete the collection, the new collection, just be sure there's the configuration that you are passing, that is 307.
Krish Naik: Out of 2 anything that you can do.
JB: I did change… I mentioned locally, Paul. Probably, I'm changing the deploy file, right, somewhere?
Krish Naik: No, in deployment, I don't think there is any place where we are using that parameter. It has to be into the code only.
JB: In court, I think I changed it.
Krish Naik: Assure me.
Krish Naik: Show me the boot, show me the boot.
JB: Okay, I'm not seeing the quota.
Krish Naik: Yes, I can only see that API screen.
Krish Naik: Okay, you want to be presenter, alright? I will add you to panelist.
JB: Can see the screen, right? I'm in code.
Krish Naik: Alright, go to config file first, config.
Krish Naik: Gemini API key is a string, alright.
Krish Naik: Okay, just wait, Gemini 2.flash is the model that you have selected.
JB: Yes.
Krish Naik: models like Gemini, okay, LLM model, this is fine.
Krish Naik: Okay. Now, go to the file where vector store was defined.
Krish Naik: vector store. You can see directly how there. Scroll below, here, embedding dimension.
Krish Naik: 3072 you have selected, no. Make it 1536.
Krish Naik: Your committed deadline, and you have… Okay.
JB: Gemini, is it not 3070?
Krish Naik: Gemini has multiple dimensions.
JB: Okay, okay.
Krish Naik: Default is the 3072.
JB: Locally, it expected us to… me to have the 307 to pull. Now it is expecting 1536. Any reason?
Krish Naik: Because 1536 is the configuration for your vector DB.
Krish Naik: when you are creating the vector store, then you are telling that I will be using this particular dimension.
Krish Naik: Yes, Koza, sir, I think you can start sharing your screen.
Krish Naik: Yes, please start sharing.
Krish Naik: Okay, I think you were already sharing, yes.
Kodali Purna Chand: Yeah, so I was, running this code.
Krish Naik: It took almost 12 minutes, consumed almost $3.
Kodali Purna Chand: Okay.
Kodali Purna Chand: This was the message I was seeing in the scroll.
Kodali Purna Chand: Is this on the right direction, or is.
Krish Naik: Yes, this is the right direction. You have done a keyboard interrupt, this is fine, but you are in the right direction.
Kodali Purna Chand: Okay, thank you. So, probably I should do it for a smaller data set.
Krish Naik: Yes, pick up something small.
Kodali Purna Chand: Yeah, thank you.
Krish Naik: Hmm.
Krish Naik: Yes, others who want to drop, just I'm looking into the issue.
Krish Naik: And go back to your code, show me the part where you are creating the dimensions, that these shown ones.
Krish Naik: I can't see the boot, I can only see the browser.
JB: Oh yeah, changing.
JB: Is this what you would like to see?
Krish Naik: Yes, just scroll down below.
Krish Naik: Quadrant Client client, quadrant API, okay, then go below vector store service, class.
Krish Naik: self.embedding, when you go to getEmbitting, click on that, get embedding.
Krish Naik: So right now, from where that call is taking place, that I want to really…
Krish Naik: So, okay, go below. Direct function call, I think.
Krish Naik: quadrant vector store, ensure the collection that happens. In that step, like, you have to do the verification once, that, whether that output from Gemini, whether it's giving you 3072 or 1536.
Krish Naik: Because your code is up and working, you just need to fix the dimension embedding issue. There are two pro… two solutions. One, you delete the collection, you create a collection with 3072 setting. The other option, you change here the emitting dimension from
Krish Naik: This one, and use the same of 1536 levels. Now, however way you solve it. Both the ways are there.
JB: Okay, sure, Paul, I'll look into this.
Krish Naik: Okay, and then let me know. If something is there, drop me a mail.
JB: Okay, sure, thank you.
JB: Thank you, Paul.
Krish Naik: Alright, so I think we are done.
Krish Naik: Alright guys, so let's meet on next Saturday, okay, and we will continue our discussion with Lama Intex. Bye-bye, everyone, thanks for joining.